[
    {
        "question": "What is NOT one of Strong Bads favorite bands in the Internet cartoon Homestar Runner?",
        "correct_answer": " sloshy",
        "answer_a": " sloshy",
        "answer_b": " Peter Frampton",
        "answer_c": " Limozeen",
        "answer_d": " Taranchula"
    },
    {
        "question": "Speaking of the famous fairy tale, that girl with the long hair was named which of these plants?",
        "correct_answer": " Rampion",
        "answer_a": " Rampion",
        "answer_b": " Turnip",
        "answer_c": " Lettuce",
        "answer_d": " Safflower"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sleeping Beauty pricked her finger on the part of a spinning wheel that does this.",
        "correct_answer": " Twists the fibres into a thread",
        "answer_a": " Collects the finished thread",
        "answer_b": " Powers the wheel",
        "answer_c": " Twists the fibres into a thread",
        "answer_d": " Sorts the finished threads"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does Cinderella wear a glass slipper?",
        "correct_answer": " Glass shoes sound like something a princess would wear.",
        "answer_a": " Glass shoes sound like something a princess would wear.",
        "answer_b": " Vair (fur), was mistaken for verre (glass).",
        "answer_c": " They were a symbol of her purity.",
        "answer_d": " Glass shoes were worn by royalty."
    },
    {
        "question": "The Little Mermaid refused to kill the prince, so she eventually ends up as this.",
        "correct_answer": " A daughter of the air.",
        "answer_a": " A block-buster animated film.",
        "answer_b": " Foam on the waves.",
        "answer_c": " A mermaid again.",
        "answer_d": " A daughter of the air."
    },
    {
        "question": "Only one of the following descriptions of the features of Snow White is true.  Can you spot it?",
        "correct_answer": " Wooden hair.",
        "answer_a": " Hemophiliac lips.",
        "answer_b": " Rosaceae cheeks.",
        "answer_c": " Ice crystal eyes.",
        "answer_d": " Wooden hair."
    },
    {
        "question": "Referring to a well-known fairy tale, the millers daughter had to spin what?",
        "correct_answer": " Dry stalks of wheat.",
        "answer_a": " Dried stalks of marsh plant.",
        "answer_b": " Dry stalks of grass.",
        "answer_c": " Dry stalks of corn.",
        "answer_d": " Dry stalks of wheat."
    },
    {
        "question": "The witch in Hansel and Gretel was probably raised in this part of the world.",
        "correct_answer": " Eastern Europe",
        "answer_a": " England",
        "answer_b": " Italy",
        "answer_c": " Eastern Europe",
        "answer_d": " The Middle East"
    },
    {
        "question": "Referring to the popular fairy tale, what is the name of the goose girls enchanted horse?",
        "correct_answer": " Falada - to speak",
        "answer_a": " Saladin - righteousness",
        "answer_b": " Fallow - pale in colour",
        "answer_c": " Falada - to speak",
        "answer_d": " Salada - white as salt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Poor Eliza of the famous fairy tale, had to make eleven shirts of what plant?",
        "correct_answer": " Urticaceae",
        "answer_a": " Belladonna",
        "answer_b": " Urticaria",
        "answer_c": " Belonidae",
        "answer_d": " Urticaceae"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many siblings does Ron have?",
        "correct_answer": " 6",
        "answer_a": " 6",
        "answer_b": " 8",
        "answer_c": " 3",
        "answer_d": " none"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Ron hate the most about himself?",
        "correct_answer": " Being poor",
        "answer_a": " Being poor",
        "answer_b": " Being the youngest boy in his family",
        "answer_c": " Being unpopular",
        "answer_d": " Not being in Slytherin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Ron take to the Yule ball?",
        "correct_answer": " Padma Patil",
        "answer_a": " Parvati Patil",
        "answer_b": " Padma Patil",
        "answer_c": " Hermione Granger",
        "answer_d": " Ginny Weasley"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rons mom is part of the order of the phoenix.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Rons full name?",
        "correct_answer": " Ronald Bilius Weasley",
        "answer_a": " Ronald Perkins Weasley",
        "answer_b": " Ronald Arthur Weasley",
        "answer_c": " Ronald J. Weasley",
        "answer_d": " Ronald Bilius Weasley"
    },
    {
        "question": "Has Ron ever been dead?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Rons idol?",
        "correct_answer": " Viktor Krum",
        "answer_a": " Oliver Wood",
        "answer_b": " Cedric Diggory",
        "answer_c": " Viktor Krum",
        "answer_d": " Harry Potter"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which of the first six books does Ron face Voldemort?",
        "correct_answer": " Never",
        "answer_a": " Goblet of Fire",
        "answer_b": " Never",
        "answer_c": " Half-Blood Prince",
        "answer_d": " Sorcerers Stone"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which charm did Doby the House Elf use to get Harry Potter in huge trouble with his Uncle?",
        "correct_answer": " A hover charm",
        "answer_a": " A clutter charm",
        "answer_b": " A disturbance charm",
        "answer_c": " A flutter charm",
        "answer_d": " A hover charm"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the full name of Harry Potters Headmaster, as revealed in the 5th book?",
        "correct_answer": " Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
        "answer_a": " Albus Abelforth Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
        "answer_b": " Albus Nicholas Abelforth Dumbledore",
        "answer_c": " Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
        "answer_d": " Albus Wulfric Nicholas Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        "question": "Aside from a bit of the person you wish to become, what are the other ingredients used to make Polyjuice Potion, as seen in the 2nd book of Harry Potter?",
        "correct_answer": " Lacewing flies, leeches, powdered bicorn horn, knotgrass, fluxweed, and boomslang skin",
        "answer_a": " Lacewing flies, leeches, powdered bicorn horn, knotgrass, fluxweed, and boomslang skin",
        "answer_b": " Porcupine quills, leeches, lacewing flies, valerian roots, and boomslang skin",
        "answer_c": " Powdered dragon horn, moonstone, lacewing flies, boomslang skin, dried nettles, and valerian roots",
        "answer_d": " Moonstone, lacewing flies, boomslang skin, dried nettles, knotgrass, and bubotuber pus"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the first task of the Triwizard Tournament (Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire ), each champion has to fight a different breed of dragon.  Which dragon does Fleur Delacour face?",
        "correct_answer": " Welsh Green",
        "answer_a": " Swedish Short-Snout",
        "answer_b": " Welsh Green",
        "answer_c": " Hungarian Horntail",
        "answer_d": " Chinese Fireball"
    },
    {
        "question": "At Harry Potters trial during the 5th book, Madam Bones refers to Harrys patronus a corporal patronus.  What makes Harrys patronus corporal?",
        "correct_answer": " His patronus is consistent enough to always have a defined shape to it",
        "answer_a": " His patronus is strong enough to complete its intended task",
        "answer_b": " His patronus is consistent enough to always have a defined shape to it",
        "answer_c": " His patronus is so dependable that it becomes the same animal everytime",
        "answer_d": " His patronus is so well developed it has a commanding presence whenever it is conjured"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potters Dudley Dursley has had many traumatic encounters with wizards.  Which of the following has not happened to him?",
        "correct_answer": " He breaks out in horrible zits",
        "answer_a": " He gets a pigs tail",
        "answer_b": " He breaks out in horrible zits",
        "answer_c": " His tongue is enlarged to almost 4 feet",
        "answer_d": " He gets attacted by dementors"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter books, Fred and George invented a lot of products for their store, Weasleys Wizard Wheezes.  Which of the following products was not one invited by Fred and George?",
        "correct_answer": " Coughing Cakes",
        "answer_a": " Self-Inking Quills",
        "answer_b": " Fever Fudge",
        "answer_c": " Coughing Cakes",
        "answer_d": " Pygmy Puff"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, Hermione is given a time turner so she is able to make it to all of her extra classes.  Which of the following classes does she not take?",
        "correct_answer": " Alchemy",
        "answer_a": " Arithmancy",
        "answer_b": " Astronomy",
        "answer_c": " Ancient Runes",
        "answer_d": " Alchemy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the last person Harry talked to in the book?",
        "correct_answer": " Hermoine",
        "answer_a": " Hermoine",
        "answer_b": " Ron",
        "answer_c": " Dumbledore",
        "answer_d": " Hagrid"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the Dursleys send Harry for Christmas?",
        "correct_answer": " A fifty pence piece",
        "answer_a": " Nothing",
        "answer_b": " An owl",
        "answer_c": " A fifty pence piece",
        "answer_d": " A sneak-o-scope"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rons sisters name is?",
        "correct_answer": " Ginny",
        "answer_a": " Ginny",
        "answer_b": " George",
        "answer_c": " Ginger",
        "answer_d": " Grace"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hermoine broke her wrist when she fell off a broom.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the poltergeist that lives at Hogwarts?",
        "correct_answer": " Peeves",
        "answer_a": " Pee-wee",
        "answer_b": " Peeves",
        "answer_c": " Pippy",
        "answer_d": " Petry"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of candy did Dumbledore offer McGonagell?",
        "correct_answer": " Lemon Drop",
        "answer_a": " Every Flavor Jellybeans",
        "answer_b": " Lemon Drop",
        "answer_c": " Cockroach Cluster",
        "answer_d": " Mr. Goodbar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dudleys gang consisted of Piers, dennis, Malcolm and Gordon.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the Muggle school Harry was to attend?",
        "correct_answer": " Stonewall High",
        "answer_a": " Stonewall High",
        "answer_b": " Yale",
        "answer_c": " Stonebridge High",
        "answer_d": " St. Brutus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Harry buy his wand?",
        "correct_answer": " Ollivanders",
        "answer_a": " Flourish  Blotts",
        "answer_b": " Ollivanders",
        "answer_c": " J.C. Penneys",
        "answer_d": " Madame Malkins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who breaks Harry Potters nose in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, the sixth novel in the series?",
        "correct_answer": " Draco Malfoy",
        "answer_a": " Proffesor Snape",
        "answer_b": " Lucious Malfoy",
        "answer_c": " Draco Malfoy",
        "answer_d": " Lord Voldemort"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Draco Malfoy attempt to kill Dumbledore in the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Initially Harry Potter and Ron did not like Hermione and considered her annoying, interfering and snobby.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Harry Potter kiss in the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, after Gryffindor wins the Quidditch Cup?",
        "correct_answer": " Ginny Weasley",
        "answer_a": " Nobody",
        "answer_b": " Ginny Weasley",
        "answer_c": " Cho Chang",
        "answer_d": " Hermione Granger"
    },
    {
        "question": "This fictional character suggests the name Dumbledores Army for the organization started by Harry, Hermione, and Ron in the book Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix.",
        "correct_answer": " Ginny Weasly",
        "answer_a": " Luna Lovegood",
        "answer_b": " Marietta Edgecombe",
        "answer_c": " Cho Chang",
        "answer_d": " Ginny Weasly"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which book of the Harry Potter series, Harry, Ron and Hermione start attending the Divination class, taught by Professor Trelawney?",
        "correct_answer": " Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban",
        "answer_a": " Harry potter and the Order of the Phoniex",
        "answer_b": " Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
        "answer_c": " Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
        "answer_d": " Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did J.K. Rowling receive an OBE (Order of the British Empire) from the Queen of England?",
        "correct_answer": " 2000",
        "answer_a": " 1999",
        "answer_b": " None of these",
        "answer_c": " 2000",
        "answer_d": " 2001"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following items cannot be found in a colonial classroom?",
        "correct_answer": " Crayon",
        "answer_a": " Quill pen",
        "answer_b": " Fireplace",
        "answer_c": " Crayon",
        "answer_d": " Horn book"
    },
    {
        "question": "Colonial people spend some of their free time doing which of these?",
        "correct_answer": " Reading McGuffey",
        "answer_a": " Skateboarding",
        "answer_b": " Using a dishwasher",
        "answer_c": " Reading McGuffey",
        "answer_d": " Ordering pizza"
    },
    {
        "question": "From age 12 to 21, American activist and politician Benjamin Franklin did what?",
        "correct_answer": " Worked as an apprentice",
        "answer_a": " Went to school",
        "answer_b": " Worked on his autobiography",
        "answer_c": " Worked on many inventions, including electricity",
        "answer_d": " Worked as an apprentice"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1889, this person founded the Hull House, one of the first settlement houses in the U.S.",
        "correct_answer": " Jane Addams",
        "answer_a": " Jane Addams",
        "answer_b": " Harriet Tubman",
        "answer_c": " Betty Ross",
        "answer_d": " Florence Nightingale"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a famous quote by John Paul Jones, the well-known American naval hero from the American Revolutionary War?",
        "correct_answer": " I have not yet begun to fight.",
        "answer_a": " I have a dream.",
        "answer_b": " Give me liberty or give me death.",
        "answer_c": " I have not yet begun to fight.",
        "answer_d": " I shall return."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following events is associated with Independence Day?",
        "correct_answer": " Declaration of Independence",
        "answer_a": " Emancipation Proclamation",
        "answer_b": " Louisiana Purchase",
        "answer_c": " Declaration of Independence",
        "answer_d": " Boston Tea Party"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Columbus first arrive on American land?",
        "correct_answer": " 1498",
        "answer_a": " 1588",
        "answer_b": " 1498",
        "answer_c": " 1600",
        "answer_d": " 1763"
    },
    {
        "question": "You can see this animal around ant-hill. It is almost 6 feet long and it likes to eat ants.",
        "correct_answer": " Anteater",
        "answer_a": " Dolphin",
        "answer_b": " Seal",
        "answer_c": " Anteater",
        "answer_d": " Kangaroo"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is a big animal with brown fur and it likes eating fish and honey. It has 42 teeth.",
        "correct_answer": " Bear",
        "answer_a": " Fox",
        "answer_b": " Bear",
        "answer_c": " Cheetah",
        "answer_d": " Horse"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is a repulsive insect either black or brown. It can live a couple of weeks with its head cut off.",
        "correct_answer": " Cockroach",
        "answer_a": " Ant",
        "answer_b": " Fly",
        "answer_c": " Cockroach",
        "answer_d": " Grasshopper"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is a big and grey animal with wide ears and a trunk. It cannot hop.",
        "correct_answer": " Elephant",
        "answer_a": " Elephant",
        "answer_b": " Rabbit",
        "answer_c": " Bear",
        "answer_d": " Horse"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is a fluffy dog. It has a black-black or purple tongue.",
        "correct_answer": " Chow Chow",
        "answer_a": " Chow Chow",
        "answer_b": " Pitbull",
        "answer_c": " Hound",
        "answer_d": " Setter"
    },
    {
        "question": "This animal lives in Africa. It has a really long neck and eats leaves. It produces almost no sounds.",
        "correct_answer": " Giraffe",
        "answer_a": " Giraffe",
        "answer_b": " Elephant",
        "answer_c": " Zebra",
        "answer_d": " Camel"
    },
    {
        "question": "This animal is similar to a mouse but it is bigger. It can give birth to more than 160 babies in a year.",
        "correct_answer": " Rat",
        "answer_a": " Cat",
        "answer_b": " Anteater",
        "answer_c": " Rat",
        "answer_d": " Weasel"
    },
    {
        "question": "These animals are long and slim. They creep. Most of them can go an entire year without eating at all!",
        "correct_answer": " Snakes",
        "answer_a": " Snakes",
        "answer_b": " Frogs",
        "answer_c": " Fish",
        "answer_d": " Eel"
    },
    {
        "question": "These animals live in the sea. They are very friendly to humans. Although they resemble fish, they will drown if kept underwater for too long.",
        "correct_answer": " Dolphins",
        "answer_a": " Mackerel",
        "answer_b": " Dolphins",
        "answer_c": " Salmon",
        "answer_d": " Tuna fish"
    },
    {
        "question": "When this animal wants to defend itself, it throws a nasty smell toward its aggressor. This smell can be detected by a human a mile away.",
        "correct_answer": " Skunk",
        "answer_a": " Skunk",
        "answer_b": " Turbot",
        "answer_c": " Horse",
        "answer_d": " Deer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which subject was Hermione not taking at 9am?",
        "correct_answer": " Potions",
        "answer_a": " Divination",
        "answer_b": " Arithmancy",
        "answer_c": " Muggle Studies",
        "answer_d": " Potions"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people where at the dinner table before Professor Trelawney joined them?",
        "correct_answer": " 12",
        "answer_a": " None of these is correct",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 13",
        "answer_d": " 12"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote A History of Magic?",
        "correct_answer": " Bathilda Bagshot",
        "answer_a": " Batgut Buckshot",
        "answer_b": " Bathilda Baghide",
        "answer_c": " Hilda Bagshot",
        "answer_d": " Bathilda Bagshot"
    },
    {
        "question": "Peter Pettigrew has his nose put in a box.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who shot gum up Peeves left nostril?",
        "correct_answer": " Professor Lupin",
        "answer_a": " Professor Lupin",
        "answer_b": " The Bloody Baron",
        "answer_c": " Harry",
        "answer_d": " Professor Lockhart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which pairing is not correct?",
        "correct_answer": " James - Antlers",
        "answer_a": " James - Antlers",
        "answer_b": " Pettigrew - Wormtail",
        "answer_c": " Lupin - Moony",
        "answer_d": " Sirius - Padfoot"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Minister of Magics name in book six?",
        "correct_answer": " Scrimgeour",
        "answer_a": " Scrimgeour",
        "answer_b": " Weasly",
        "answer_c": " Umbridge",
        "answer_d": " Fudge"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Tonks in love with?",
        "correct_answer": " Lupin",
        "answer_a": " no one",
        "answer_b": " Bill",
        "answer_c": " Lupin",
        "answer_d": " Ron"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has the hots for Harry in the first half of the book?",
        "correct_answer": " Romilda",
        "answer_a": " Ginny",
        "answer_b": " Luna",
        "answer_c": " Romilda",
        "answer_d": " Cho"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which potion did Harry make to win a bottle of Liquid Luckin Chapter 9?",
        "correct_answer": " Draught of Living Death",
        "answer_a": " Veritaserum",
        "answer_b": " Draught of Living Death",
        "answer_c": " Draught of Death",
        "answer_d": " Felix Felicis"
    },
    {
        "question": "She is Tom Riddles mother.",
        "correct_answer": " Merope",
        "answer_a": " Lily",
        "answer_b": " Mekare",
        "answer_c": " Jane",
        "answer_d": " Merope"
    },
    {
        "question": "This was the password to the Griffindore Tower after Christmas break.",
        "correct_answer": " abstinence",
        "answer_a": " abysmal",
        "answer_b": " caput draconis",
        "answer_c": " abstinence",
        "answer_d": " abstraction"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was not at Hermiones table in Herbology?",
        "correct_answer": " Neville",
        "answer_a": " Neville",
        "answer_b": " Ron",
        "answer_c": " They all were",
        "answer_d": " Harry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tom Riddle worked for Florrish and Blott after he left Hogwarts.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the author of the Harry Potter series of books?",
        "correct_answer": " J.K. Rowling",
        "answer_a": " J.R. Rolling",
        "answer_b": " J.R. Tolkien",
        "answer_c": " J.K. Rowling",
        "answer_d": " Gilderoy Lockhart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, the second book in the Harry Potter series, was published in what year?",
        "correct_answer": " 1998",
        "answer_a": " 2000",
        "answer_b": " 1989",
        "answer_c": " 2001",
        "answer_d": " 1998"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, during the summer break Harry gets a visit from a character named Dobby. What kind of creature is Dobby?",
        "correct_answer": " a house elf",
        "answer_a": " a house dwarf",
        "answer_b": " a house Imp",
        "answer_c": " a house nymph",
        "answer_d": " a house elf"
    },
    {
        "question": "This fictional character, introduced in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, was teacher of the class called Defense Against the Dark Artsand five-time winner of Witch Weeklys Most Charming Smile Award.",
        "correct_answer": " Gilderoy Lockhart",
        "answer_a": " Lupin",
        "answer_b": " Stan Shunpike",
        "answer_c": " Gilderoy Lockhart",
        "answer_d": " Rowling"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry and Ron take a ride with the flying Ford Anglia and crash into what kind of tree?",
        "correct_answer": " a whomping willow tree",
        "answer_a": " a black willow tree",
        "answer_b": " a whomping willow tree",
        "answer_c": " a deadwood Tree",
        "answer_d": " a weeping willow tree"
    },
    {
        "question": "This fictional character from the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets is a ghost ,who haunts the second floor girls lavatory at Hogwarts School for Witchcraft and Wizardry.",
        "correct_answer": " Moaning Myrtle",
        "answer_a": " Moaning Molly",
        "answer_b": " Moaning Martha",
        "answer_c": " Moaning Myrtle",
        "answer_d": " Moaning Mary"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character of the Harry Potter series of books opens the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " Ginny Weasley",
        "answer_a": " Cho Chang",
        "answer_b": " None of these",
        "answer_c": " Draco Malfoy",
        "answer_d": " Ginny Weasley"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the language of snakes, spoken by some of the characters in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " parseltongue",
        "answer_a": " parseltongue",
        "answer_b": " none of these",
        "answer_c": " parsellanguage",
        "answer_d": " parselspeak"
    },
    {
        "question": "The fictional Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry is geographically located in which part of the United Kingdom?",
        "correct_answer": " Scotland",
        "answer_a": " Wales",
        "answer_b": " Scotland",
        "answer_c": " England",
        "answer_d": " Northern Ireland"
    },
    {
        "question": "How is the wizarding worlds newspaper, The Daily Prophet, delivered each morning in the Harry Potter novels?",
        "correct_answer": " Owl post",
        "answer_a": " Workers of the Postal Union 151",
        "answer_b": " Owl post",
        "answer_c": " United Parcel Service",
        "answer_d": " Postal carriage"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the Harry Potter books, the Floo Network, or traveling using floo powder, means using what method of transportation?",
        "correct_answer": " Fireplaces",
        "answer_a": " Internet",
        "answer_b": " Fireplaces",
        "answer_c": " Toilets",
        "answer_d": " Fedex"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following animals does NOT symbolize one of the four Hogwarts Houses, described in the Harry Potter series of books?",
        "correct_answer": " Panda",
        "answer_a": " Eagle",
        "answer_b": " Panda",
        "answer_c": " Serpent",
        "answer_d": " Lion"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hagrid, the keeper of the keys at Hogwarts in the Harry Potter books, lives in this building on the edge of the Forbidden Forest.",
        "correct_answer": " Wooden cabin",
        "answer_a": " 750 meter highrise, which is the tallest building in the wizarding world.",
        "answer_b": " Wigwam",
        "answer_c": " Wooden cabin",
        "answer_d": " A miniature copy of the Tower of Piza"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what type of vehicle did Ron and Harry Potter fly to Hogwarts from London?",
        "correct_answer": " Ford Anglia",
        "answer_a": " Ford Anglia",
        "answer_b": " Apache helicopter",
        "answer_c": " Boeing 767",
        "answer_d": " Flying carpet"
    },
    {
        "question": "While looking for the Sorcerers Stone, Ron and Harry Potter must play a life-size version of this game.",
        "correct_answer": " Chess",
        "answer_a": " Monopoly",
        "answer_b": " Checkers",
        "answer_c": " Chess",
        "answer_d": " Scrabble"
    },
    {
        "question": "This flying machine was owned by Sirius Black and used by Hagrid in his first appearance on Privet Drive.",
        "correct_answer": " Motorcycle",
        "answer_a": " Hydroplane",
        "answer_b": " Motorcycle",
        "answer_c": " Lamborghini",
        "answer_d": " Hot air balloon"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter universe, a hippogriff is a hybrid of what two animals?",
        "correct_answer": " An eagle and a horse",
        "answer_a": " A hippopotamus and a vulture",
        "answer_b": " An eagle and a lion",
        "answer_c": " A hawk and a donkey",
        "answer_d": " An eagle and a horse"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter books, if a person is a parselmouth, then he or she is able to understand what?",
        "correct_answer": " Snakes",
        "answer_a": " Women",
        "answer_b": " Snakes",
        "answer_c": " Centaurs",
        "answer_d": " Elfs"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do the rings on a tree tell us?",
        "correct_answer": " how old the tree is",
        "answer_a": " how tall the tree is",
        "answer_b": " how old the tree is",
        "answer_c": " whether or not it is a fruit bearing tree",
        "answer_d": " what type of tree it is"
    },
    {
        "question": "The path in which electricity travels is called an electric circuit.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Seasons change because the Earth is getting closer and further from the sun.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stars vanish during the day.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 4 basic conditions needed to produce an echo.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the names of the four children in the story The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
        "correct_answer": " Peter, Susan, Edmund, Lucy",
        "answer_a": " Peter, Annie, Alan, Lucy",
        "answer_b": " Peter, Susan, Edmund, Sydney",
        "answer_c": " Peter, Susan, Edmund, Lucy",
        "answer_d": " Peter, Sally, Edward, Lucinda"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character is the enemy of the four children in the movie The Chronicles of Narnia: The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
        "correct_answer": " The White Witch",
        "answer_a": " The Red Witch",
        "answer_b": " The Evil Witch",
        "answer_c": " The Terrible Witch of the West",
        "answer_d": " The White Witch"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, Susan is the oldest of the four children.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe Edmund asked if the White Witch had what candy?",
        "correct_answer": " Turkish Delight",
        "answer_a": " Turkish Delight",
        "answer_b": " Laffy Taffy",
        "answer_c": " Jolly Rancher",
        "answer_d": " Turkish Joy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that in the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, Lucy discovered the wardrobe, while the children were playing hide and seek?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the colour of Susans eyes in the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
        "correct_answer": " blue",
        "answer_a": " green",
        "answer_b": " brown",
        "answer_c": " hazel",
        "answer_d": " blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Peter the second of the Pevensie children to enter Narnia in the film The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "The action in the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe begins in 1940 during a German bombing raid of London.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the faun that Lucy meets in The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
        "correct_answer": " Tumnus",
        "answer_a": " Taurus",
        "answer_b": " Tamus",
        "answer_c": " Tumnus",
        "answer_d": " Timus"
    },
    {
        "question": "The lion that the children meet in the end of the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobeis called Aslan.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following characters in the Harry Potter books is a poltergeist?",
        "correct_answer": " Peeves",
        "answer_a": " Moaning Myrthle",
        "answer_b": " Peeves",
        "answer_c": " Nearly-headless Nick",
        "answer_d": " The Bloody Baron"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the potion that grants good luck, mentioned in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Felix Felicis",
        "answer_a": " Felix Felicis",
        "answer_b": " Polyjuice Potion",
        "answer_c": " none of these",
        "answer_d": " Avada Kedava"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these characters kissed Harry after a lesson of DA in Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?",
        "correct_answer": " Cho",
        "answer_a": " Hermione",
        "answer_b": " Cho",
        "answer_c": " Ginny",
        "answer_d": " Blaise"
    },
    {
        "question": "What group did Nearly-headless Nick never become a part of in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " The Headless Hunt",
        "answer_a": " The Order of the Phoenix",
        "answer_b": " The Headless Hunt",
        "answer_c": " The Triwizard Cup",
        "answer_d": " The DA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following characters are described as trustworthy in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " James Potter, Remus Lupin, Sirius Black",
        "answer_a": " James Potter, Remus Lupin, Sirius Black",
        "answer_b": " James Potter, Remus Lupin",
        "answer_c": " James Potter, Sirius Black, Peter Pettigrew",
        "answer_d": " James Potter only"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the Harry Potter books, what is the full name of Dumbledore, the headmaster of Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry?",
        "correct_answer": " Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
        "answer_a": " Albus Percival Dumbledore",
        "answer_b": " Albus Wulfric Dumbledore",
        "answer_c": " Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
        "answer_d": " He never revealed his full name in the books"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dumbledore was in contact with Sirius Black in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, the half-blood prince tells Harry to do what to his potion?",
        "correct_answer": " Add a clockwise stir after every seventh counterclockwise stir",
        "answer_a": " Stir clockwise until the potion turns as clear as water",
        "answer_b": " Add a counterclockwise stir after every seventh clockwise stir",
        "answer_c": " Stir counterclockwise until the potion turns as clear as water",
        "answer_d": " Add a clockwise stir after every seventh counterclockwise stir"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of creature was Buckbeak from the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " Hippogriff",
        "answer_a": " Manticore",
        "answer_b": " Unicorn",
        "answer_c": " Hippogriff",
        "answer_d": " Bird"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the last person to talk to Harry at the end of Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " Hermione",
        "answer_a": " Dudley",
        "answer_b": " Ron",
        "answer_c": " Hermione",
        "answer_d": " Ms. Weasley"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter books, what is the name of Hagrids three-headed dog?",
        "correct_answer": " Fluffy",
        "answer_a": " Fluffy",
        "answer_b": " Norbert",
        "answer_c": " Aragog",
        "answer_d": " Fang"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the Harry Potter books, who is Harrys godfather?",
        "correct_answer": " Sirius Black",
        "answer_a": " Sirius Black",
        "answer_b": " Remus Lupin",
        "answer_c": " Peter Pettigrew",
        "answer_d": " James Potter"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what book of the Harry Potter series does professor Trelawney get fired?",
        "correct_answer": " Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix",
        "answer_a": " Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone",
        "answer_b": " Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
        "answer_c": " Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix",
        "answer_d": " She doesnt get fired in the books"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter books, what is Harrys classmate Hermiones full name?",
        "correct_answer": " Hermione Jean Granger",
        "answer_a": " Hermione Cassandra Granger",
        "answer_b": " It was never mentioned.",
        "answer_c": " Hermione James Dumbledore",
        "answer_d": " Hermione Jean Granger"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which movie did Hermione Granger say the following:",
        "correct_answer": " Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone",
        "answer_a": " Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban",
        "answer_b": " Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
        "answer_c": " Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
        "answer_d": " Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Hermione Granger, a character from the Harry Potter series, think about the Firebolt?",
        "correct_answer": " that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Sirius Black",
        "answer_a": " that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Sirius Black",
        "answer_b": " that it was given to Harry by Dumbledore because he felt bad after Harrys broom was demolished by the Whomping Willow",
        "answer_c": " that it was amazing and wanted to be the first to ride it after Harry",
        "answer_d": " that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Lucius Malfoy who was still angry about the loss of his House Elf"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is stated in the Harry Potter books that Hermione Grangers parents are teachers.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was Hermione able to see the Thresals in Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter series, Hermiones full name is Hermione Denise Granger.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the wooden stick used to hit a baseball called?",
        "correct_answer": " Baseball Bat",
        "answer_a": " Baseball Wand",
        "answer_b": " Baseball Bat",
        "answer_c": " Baseball Raquet",
        "answer_d": " Baseball Club"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is a major league baseball?",
        "correct_answer": " White",
        "answer_a": " Green",
        "answer_b": " White",
        "answer_c": " Black",
        "answer_d": " Blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "Should you wear a helmet while hitting a baseball?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is it called when you hit a baseball out of the park?",
        "correct_answer": " Home Run",
        "answer_a": " Home Run",
        "answer_b": " Stolen Base",
        "answer_c": " Hat Trick",
        "answer_d": " 3 Pointer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you wear on your hand when playing the field in baseball?",
        "correct_answer": " Baseball Glove",
        "answer_a": " Baseball Helmet",
        "answer_b": " Baseball Glove",
        "answer_c": " Baseball Mittens",
        "answer_d": " Baseball Shoes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In baseball, what is the name of the player who squats behind the hitter and catches the ball?",
        "correct_answer": " Catcher",
        "answer_a": " Catcher",
        "answer_b": " Short Stop",
        "answer_c": " Manager",
        "answer_d": " Pitcher"
    },
    {
        "question": "When you run the bases in baseball you should run from 3rd base to 1st base.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the player who throws the ball to the hitter called in baseball?",
        "correct_answer": " Pitcher",
        "answer_a": " Coach",
        "answer_b": " Catcher",
        "answer_c": " Short Stop",
        "answer_d": " Pitcher"
    },
    {
        "question": "Baseball is usually played indoors.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Casey has 2 ten dollar bills, 3 five dollar bills, and 4 one dollar bills. How much money does Casey have altogether?",
        "correct_answer": " $39",
        "answer_a": " $44",
        "answer_b": " $35",
        "answer_c": " $39",
        "answer_d": " $37"
    },
    {
        "question": "What would be next in this pattern:  XX, XXXX, XXXXXX, ________?",
        "correct_answer": " XXXXXXXX",
        "answer_a": " XXXXXXXX",
        "answer_b": " XXXXXXX",
        "answer_c": " XXXXXXXXX",
        "answer_d": " XXXXXXXXXX"
    },
    {
        "question": "Reeses Pieces cost $0.60. Nerds cost $0.35. Pepsi costs $0.90. Gum costs $0.45. I have $1.25, and want to spend all of my money. What should I buy?",
        "correct_answer": " Pepsi and Nerds",
        "answer_a": " Reeses Pieces, Nerds, and Gum",
        "answer_b": " Pepsi and Gum",
        "answer_c": " Pepsi and Nerds",
        "answer_d": " Reeses Pieces and Gum"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chad and Jason have a collection of comic books. Chad has 23 books. Together, Chad and Jason have a total of 59 books. How many books does Jason have?",
        "correct_answer": " 36",
        "answer_a": " 26",
        "answer_b": " 35",
        "answer_c": " 36",
        "answer_d": " 82"
    },
    {
        "question": "Leah is making chocolate chip cookies. She has 6 groups of 5 chocolate chips each. If she adds one more group of 5 chocolate chips, how many chocolate chips will she have?",
        "correct_answer": " 35",
        "answer_a": " 30",
        "answer_b": " 35",
        "answer_c": " 45",
        "answer_d": " 40"
    },
    {
        "question": "Stephanie has $0.85. She gives a quarter to Jennifer. In return, Jennifer gives Stephanie a dime. How much money does Stephanie have now?",
        "correct_answer": " $0.70",
        "answer_a": " $0.60",
        "answer_b": " $0.65",
        "answer_c": " $0.70",
        "answer_d": " $0.75"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mike has to be to school at 8:00 a.m. If it takes him 25 minutes to walk to school, what time should he leave?",
        "correct_answer": " 7:35 a.m.",
        "answer_a": " 7:35 a.m.",
        "answer_b": " 7:45 a.m.",
        "answer_c": " 8:25 a.m",
        "answer_d": " 7:25 a.m."
    },
    {
        "question": "The Chronicles of Narnia, written by C.S. Lewis, is a series of seven fantasy novels. Which of the following is not one of the books in this series?",
        "correct_answer": " The Boy and His Horse",
        "answer_a": " Prince Caspian",
        "answer_b": " The Boy and His Horse",
        "answer_c": " The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe",
        "answer_d": " The Voyage of the Dawn Treader"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, published in 1952, Edmund and Lucy Pevensie return to Narnia along with their younger cousin named what?",
        "correct_answer": " Eustace",
        "answer_a": " Caspian",
        "answer_b": " Telmar",
        "answer_c": " Eustace",
        "answer_d": " Digory"
    },
    {
        "question": "There comes a point when Peter, Susan, Edmund, and Lucy Pevensie are no longer allowed to visit Narnia because they are too old. So the lion calls their young cousin back to Narnia together with Jill, a fellow student of his. This happens in which book of The Chronicles of Narnia series?",
        "correct_answer": " The Silver Chair",
        "answer_a": " The Last Battle",
        "answer_b": " Prince Caspian",
        "answer_c": " The Voyage of the Dawn Treader",
        "answer_d": " The Silver Chair"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the Pevensie children is lured into teaming up with the White Witch in the novel The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
        "correct_answer": " Edmund",
        "answer_a": " Lucy",
        "answer_b": " Susan",
        "answer_c": " Edmund",
        "answer_d": " Peter"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Last Battle chronicles, which earned C.S. Lewis a Carnegie Medal, two children return to save Narnia from Shift who tricks the donkey Puzzle into impersonating the Great Lion. What kind of creature is Shift?",
        "correct_answer": " Ape",
        "answer_a": " Ape",
        "answer_b": " Centaur",
        "answer_c": " Unicorn",
        "answer_d": " Faun"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can Bungy the budgie do?",
        "correct_answer": " water ski",
        "answer_a": " water ski",
        "answer_b": " bungy jump",
        "answer_c": " walk a tightrope",
        "answer_d": " snow ski"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sent Harry a letter in Chapter 2 telling him not to do any more magic, or to surrender his wand?",
        "correct_answer": " Arthur Weasley",
        "answer_a": " Hermione",
        "answer_b": " Sirius Black",
        "answer_c": " Arthur Weasley",
        "answer_d": " Molly Weasley"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cornelius Fudge thinks that who wants to be the Minister of Magic?",
        "correct_answer": " Albus Dumbledore",
        "answer_a": " Sirius Black",
        "answer_b": " Lucius Malfoy",
        "answer_c": " Arthur Weasly",
        "answer_d": " Albus Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        "question": "This person is Siriuss brother.",
        "correct_answer": " Regulus",
        "answer_a": " Regulus",
        "answer_b": " Tom",
        "answer_c": " Ronald",
        "answer_d": " Remus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Luna Lovegood was reading the Quippler on the Hogwarts Express.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ward was Arthur Weasly in while at St Mungos?",
        "correct_answer": " Llewellyn",
        "answer_a": " Llewellyn",
        "answer_b": " Corwin",
        "answer_c": " Blaise",
        "answer_d": " Diedre"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is Professor Umbridges middle name.",
        "correct_answer": " Jane",
        "answer_a": " Jane",
        "answer_b": " Marie",
        "answer_c": " Barbara",
        "answer_d": " Mary"
    },
    {
        "question": "A giant chief is called this.",
        "correct_answer": " Gurg",
        "answer_a": " Urg",
        "answer_b": " Gurg",
        "answer_c": " Gurrl",
        "answer_d": " Ugh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who had Neville Longbottom seen die?",
        "correct_answer": " his Grandfather",
        "answer_a": " his Grandmother",
        "answer_b": " no one",
        "answer_c": " his Grandfather",
        "answer_d": " his parents"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who did not go with Harry to the Ministry of Magic to rescue Black?",
        "correct_answer": " Cho",
        "answer_a": " Cho",
        "answer_b": " Neville",
        "answer_c": " Luna",
        "answer_d": " Ron"
    },
    {
        "question": "Josh and Parker star on this Nickelodeon show which takes place mostly at a fast food restaurant. What is the name of the show?",
        "correct_answer": " Mr. Meaty",
        "answer_a": " Mr. Fast Food",
        "answer_b": " Mr. Meaty",
        "answer_c": " Mr. Meat",
        "answer_d": " Dr. Burger"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these Nickelodeon animated shows stars a big headed kid who also has a very big brain?",
        "correct_answer": " Jimmy Neutron",
        "answer_a": " Jimmy Neutron",
        "answer_b": " Drake and Josh",
        "answer_c": " Neutron, Boy Genius",
        "answer_d": " The fairly odd parents"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the show Jimmy Neutron, Jimmy goes to Mars in search of a major power source and runs into some huge rock creatures living on Mars. What substance are these creatures vulnerable to?",
        "correct_answer": " Water",
        "answer_a": " Water",
        "answer_b": " Fire",
        "answer_c": " Air",
        "answer_d": " Light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Actor Drake Bell from the Nickelodeon show Drake and Josh founded a band named Drake 24/7 in real life.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Neds Declassified School Survival Guide, who dares Moze to wear a frilly dress with flowers for 48 hours?",
        "correct_answer": " Nobody dares her that",
        "answer_a": " Ned Bigby",
        "answer_b": " Simon Nelson Cook",
        "answer_c": " Nobody dares her that",
        "answer_d": " Billy Loomer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Actress Miranda Cosgrove plays Megan in the hit Nickelodeon show Drake and Josh.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Complete this line from the classic childrens book Green Eggs and Ham:",
        "correct_answer": " Sam",
        "answer_a": " A Lamb",
        "answer_b": " Jean-Claude Van Damme",
        "answer_c": " Sam",
        "answer_d": " Bam-Bam"
    },
    {
        "question": "The book Green Eggs and Ham was first published in 1952.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did Green Eggs and Ham rank according to Publishers Weekly 2001 list of best selling childrens books of all-time?",
        "correct_answer": " Fourth",
        "answer_a": " Fourth",
        "answer_b": " Second",
        "answer_c": " First",
        "answer_d": " Third"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rev. Jesse Jackson once read Green Eggs and Ham aloud on the late Night show Saturday Night Live.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Complete this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham:",
        "correct_answer": " Fox",
        "answer_a": " Dog with Chicken Pox",
        "answer_b": " Bag of Rocks",
        "answer_c": " Clock",
        "answer_d": " Fox"
    },
    {
        "question": "The book Green Eggs and Ham contains only 50 different words.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What word is missing in this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham:",
        "correct_answer": " Car",
        "answer_a": " Line at the DMV",
        "answer_b": " Jeep",
        "answer_c": " Bucket of boiled beets",
        "answer_d": " Car"
    },
    {
        "question": "What should you wear on your head when you play American football?",
        "correct_answer": " Helmet",
        "answer_a": " Hat",
        "answer_b": " Helmet",
        "answer_c": " Wig",
        "answer_d": " Shoe"
    },
    {
        "question": "In American football, the player who throws the ball to the other players on the field is called what?",
        "correct_answer": " Quarterback",
        "answer_a": " Quarterback",
        "answer_b": " Running back",
        "answer_c": " Kicker",
        "answer_d": " Tight End"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these items is not used in an American football game?",
        "correct_answer": " Stick",
        "answer_a": " Helmet",
        "answer_b": " Stick",
        "answer_c": " Padding",
        "answer_d": " Football"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the main method of scoring in American football?",
        "correct_answer": " Touchdown",
        "answer_a": " Touchdown",
        "answer_b": " Three Pointer",
        "answer_c": " Home Run",
        "answer_d": " Hat Trick"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the professional team of Miami in American football called?",
        "correct_answer": " Dolphins",
        "answer_a": " Patriots",
        "answer_b": " Dolphins",
        "answer_c": " Yankees",
        "answer_d": " Jets"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call the grassy area on which an American football game is played?",
        "correct_answer": " Field",
        "answer_a": " Court",
        "answer_b": " Rink",
        "answer_c": " Diamond",
        "answer_d": " Field"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the color of a traditional American football?",
        "correct_answer": " Brown and white",
        "answer_a": " Brown and white",
        "answer_b": " Green and yellow",
        "answer_c": " Pink and purple",
        "answer_d": " Blue and red"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many points is a touchdown worth in American football?",
        "correct_answer": " 6",
        "answer_a": " 2",
        "answer_b": " 4",
        "answer_c": " 5",
        "answer_d": " 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the shape of a traditional American football?",
        "correct_answer": " Oval",
        "answer_a": " Rectangle",
        "answer_b": " Square",
        "answer_c": " Oval",
        "answer_d": " Round"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call the man or woman who runs a football team and tells the players what to do?",
        "correct_answer": " Coach",
        "answer_a": " Wide Receiver",
        "answer_b": " Quarterback",
        "answer_c": " Tight End",
        "answer_d": " Coach"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did Disney release the film The Little Mermaid?",
        "correct_answer": " 1989",
        "answer_a": " 1889",
        "answer_b": " 1985",
        "answer_c": " 1989",
        "answer_d": " 1885"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the housemaid that served dinner on Ariels first night in the palace in the movie The Little Mermaid?",
        "correct_answer": " Carlotta",
        "answer_a": " Marianne",
        "answer_b": " Vanessa",
        "answer_c": " Janice",
        "answer_d": " Carlotta"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ursula, one of the characters in the Disney movie The Little Mermaid, is a cecaelia sea witch.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What name did Ursula adopt while in disguise in the movie The Little Mermaid?",
        "correct_answer": " Vanessa",
        "answer_a": " Matilda",
        "answer_b": " Vanessa",
        "answer_c": " Gertrude",
        "answer_d": " Louise"
    },
    {
        "question": "Buddy Hackett provided the voice of Flounder in the movie The Little Mermaid.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "The film The Little Mermaid grossed approximately $200,000,000.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first line in the movie The Little Mermaid was Flounder, quit being such a guppy!.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was the film The Little Mermaid released in Germany?",
        "correct_answer": " Nov. 29 1990",
        "answer_a": " Nov. 18 1989",
        "answer_b": " Nov. 29 1990",
        "answer_c": " Nov. 15 1989",
        "answer_d": " Nov. 15 1990"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, when Harry went to his potions class the first time that year, there were 4 potions on Mr. Slughorns desk. What were they called?",
        "correct_answer": " Veritaserum, Felix felicis, Amortentia and Poly juice potion",
        "answer_a": " Veritaserum, Felix felicis, Amortentia and Poly juice potion",
        "answer_b": " Veritaserum, hurnslug, setumaniea and felkamena",
        "answer_c": " Poly juice potion, majoina, conastance and cenputok",
        "answer_d": " Draught of the living death, milliitinie, carnaogdhor and gononala"
    },
    {
        "question": "McLaggen, who was first introduced in Harry Potter and the Half Blood Prince hit Harry in the back of his head with a wooden bat.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was Ron poisoned in the book Harry Potter and the Half-blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, Harry almost killed Malfoy.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is it true that Mrs. Arabella Figg, a character from the Harry Potter books, is a Squib?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, was the horcrux Dumbledore and Harry recovered fake?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who went first into the barrier in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " Percy",
        "answer_a": " Ron",
        "answer_b": " Fred and George",
        "answer_c": " Percy",
        "answer_d": " Harry"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the book which Ron gave Harry for Christmas in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " Flying with the Cannons",
        "answer_a": " Flying with the Cannons",
        "answer_b": " Gold Stars - How do they do it?",
        "answer_c": " Fantastic Beasts and Where to Find them",
        "answer_d": " Quidditch through the ages"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Dudley want Harry to pass him at breakfast in chapter 1 of Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " bacon",
        "answer_a": " bacon",
        "answer_b": " waffles",
        "answer_c": " pancakes",
        "answer_d": " eggs"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the title of chapter 11 of the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " The Dueling Club",
        "answer_a": " Quidditch",
        "answer_b": " The Dueling Club",
        "answer_c": " The Writing on the Wall",
        "answer_d": " The Rogue Bludger"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, what did Ron keep on doing to his Charms homework?",
        "correct_answer": " dropping ink blots on it",
        "answer_a": " scribbling on it",
        "answer_b": " poking holes in it",
        "answer_c": " making finger prints on it",
        "answer_d": " dropping ink blots on it"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first spell cast at the dueling match in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " Expelliarmus",
        "answer_a": " Sarpensortia",
        "answer_b": " Wingardium Leviosa",
        "answer_c": " Expelliarmus",
        "answer_d": " Rictusempra"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Tom Riddles diary falls into whose hands?",
        "correct_answer": " Ginnys",
        "answer_a": " Rons",
        "answer_b": " Hermiones",
        "answer_c": " Ginnys",
        "answer_d": " Harrys"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Malfoy want to be headmaster in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " Professor Snape",
        "answer_a": " Professor Snape",
        "answer_b": " Professor McGonagall",
        "answer_c": " himself",
        "answer_d": " his dad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does 10 X 10 give 100?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much is 1 + 1?",
        "correct_answer": " 2",
        "answer_a": " 2",
        "answer_b": " 11",
        "answer_c": " 4",
        "answer_d": " 3"
    },
    {
        "question": "If I have ten apples and I give them all to another person, how many do I have left?",
        "correct_answer": " 0",
        "answer_a": " 9",
        "answer_b": " 0",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you put 1 gram of steel on one scale and 1 gram of feathers on another one, which one would weigh more?",
        "correct_answer": " They would be equal",
        "answer_a": " The steel",
        "answer_b": " The feathers",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " They would be equal"
    },
    {
        "question": "If Joe had $900 dollars in life savings and he bought a refrigerator for $600 dollars, how much money would he have left?",
        "correct_answer": " $300",
        "answer_a": " $200",
        "answer_b": " $350",
        "answer_c": " $300",
        "answer_d": " $400"
    },
    {
        "question": "3.2 are the first numbers in the important mathematical constant pi.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In mathematics, is a right angle equal to 100 degrees?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the final result of the following equation: 3 X 6 X 9 X 0 X 12 X 32 X 2 = ?",
        "correct_answer": " 0",
        "answer_a": " 124,416",
        "answer_b": " 9999999",
        "answer_c": " 0",
        "answer_d": " 124,934"
    },
    {
        "question": "100 multiplied by 0.3 gives 3.00.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is NOT part of the full name of the fictional character Albus Dumbledore?",
        "correct_answer": " Roderick",
        "answer_a": " Brian",
        "answer_b": " Percival",
        "answer_c": " Roderick",
        "answer_d": " Wulfric"
    },
    {
        "question": "After graduating from the fictional Hogwarts school, Albus Dumbledore went on to teach this class before becoming headmaster.",
        "correct_answer": " Transfiguration",
        "answer_a": " Defense Against the Dark Arts",
        "answer_b": " Transfiguration",
        "answer_c": " Care of Magical Creatures",
        "answer_d": " Potions"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the Harry Potter books Albus Dumbledore liked Dementors.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince we find out that Albus Dumbledore destroyed one of Voldemorts horcruxes. In what item was the horcrux contained?",
        "correct_answer": " Ring",
        "answer_a": " Ring",
        "answer_b": " Diary",
        "answer_c": " Necklace",
        "answer_d": " Sword"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter series, one of Albus Dumbledores closest friends and companions is Fawkes, a creature that resides in Dumbledores office. What kind of creature is Fawkes?",
        "correct_answer": " Phoenix",
        "answer_a": " Owl",
        "answer_b": " Phoenix",
        "answer_c": " Demon",
        "answer_d": " Mouse"
    },
    {
        "question": "Professor Albus Dumbledores office at the fictional Hogwarts school is protected by a statue of a gargoyle.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Albus Dumbledores favorite flavor of jam as revealed in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Raspberry",
        "answer_a": " Raspberry",
        "answer_b": " Blueberry",
        "answer_c": " Blackberry",
        "answer_d": " Strawberry"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the opposite of cold?",
        "correct_answer": " hot",
        "answer_a": " humid",
        "answer_b": " hot",
        "answer_c": " dry",
        "answer_d": " wet"
    },
    {
        "question": "The opposite of open is closed.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the opposite of wrong?",
        "correct_answer": " right",
        "answer_a": " blue",
        "answer_b": " right",
        "answer_c": " maybe",
        "answer_d": " farm"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the opposite of happy?",
        "correct_answer": " sad",
        "answer_a": " missing",
        "answer_b": " sad",
        "answer_c": " purple",
        "answer_d": " mad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following words is NOT an opposite of big?",
        "correct_answer": " huge",
        "answer_a": " small",
        "answer_b": " little",
        "answer_c": " huge",
        "answer_d": " miniscule"
    },
    {
        "question": "A word with a meaning opposite to that of another word is called a synonym.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "The opposite of major is minor.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the opposite of above?",
        "correct_answer": " below",
        "answer_a": " top",
        "answer_b": " beside",
        "answer_c": " below",
        "answer_d": " green"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were the first names of Harry Potters parents?",
        "correct_answer": " Lilly, James",
        "answer_a": " Abbie, Harry",
        "answer_b": " Liiy, Harry",
        "answer_c": " Lilly, James",
        "answer_d": " Abbie, James"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these characters is Harry Potters best friend?",
        "correct_answer": " Ron",
        "answer_a": " Dudley",
        "answer_b": " Ron",
        "answer_c": " George",
        "answer_d": " Fred"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following are Harry Potters enemies at school?",
        "correct_answer": " Malfoy, Snape",
        "answer_a": " Sirius, Remus",
        "answer_b": " Malfoy, Neville",
        "answer_c": " Dumbledore, Snape",
        "answer_d": " Malfoy, Snape"
    },
    {
        "question": "Although Harry Potter has a crush on Cho Chang, he ends up with Ginny.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Daniel Radcliffe portray Harry Potter?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the potions teacher during Harry Potters sixth year at Hogwarts?",
        "correct_answer": " Horace Slughorn",
        "answer_a": " Albus Dumbledoor",
        "answer_b": " Fred Weasley",
        "answer_c": " Serverus Snape",
        "answer_d": " Horace Slughorn"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional character Ron Weasley has male siblings only.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter books, Professor Binns is a ghost that teaches History of Magic.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who accused Hermione of having a thing for famous wizards in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire?",
        "correct_answer": " Rita Skeeter",
        "answer_a": " Madame Maxime",
        "answer_b": " Mr. Crouch",
        "answer_c": " Ludo Bagman",
        "answer_d": " Rita Skeeter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Lord Voldemorts real name?",
        "correct_answer": " Tom Marvolo Riddle",
        "answer_a": " Tom Voldemort Riddle",
        "answer_b": " Tom Marvolo Riddle",
        "answer_c": " Tom Marvolo Gaunt",
        "answer_d": " Voldemort Tom Riddle"
    },
    {
        "question": "This continent is where Canada, The United States of America, and Mexico are located.",
        "correct_answer": " North America",
        "answer_a": " Europe",
        "answer_b": " South America",
        "answer_c": " North America",
        "answer_d": " Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "This ocean is bordered by North and South America on the west and Europe and Africa on the east.",
        "correct_answer": " Atlantic",
        "answer_a": " Indian",
        "answer_b": " Atlantic",
        "answer_c": " Arctic",
        "answer_d": " Pacific"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter series, Hagrid got kicked out of Hogwarts for possessing what giant creature?",
        "correct_answer": " A giant spider",
        "answer_a": " A griffon",
        "answer_b": " A giant spider",
        "answer_c": " A basilisk",
        "answer_d": " Crumple Horned Snorkak"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter books, Hagrid was forbidden to use an actual wand. What did he use instead?",
        "correct_answer": " A pink umbrella",
        "answer_a": " A pink umbrella",
        "answer_b": " A cane",
        "answer_c": " A tree branch",
        "answer_d": " A walking stick"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hagrid from the Harry Potter series once cared for a creature named Norbert. What was Norbert?",
        "correct_answer": " A dragon",
        "answer_a": " A three-headed dog",
        "answer_b": " A giant Spider",
        "answer_c": " A hippogriff",
        "answer_d": " A dragon"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter series Hagrid gets this flying object from Sirius Black and uses it as his main form of transport.",
        "correct_answer": " A motorcycle",
        "answer_a": " A Carpet",
        "answer_b": " A motorcycle",
        "answer_c": " A ship",
        "answer_d": " A broom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hagrid dies in the last installment of the Harry Potter series entitled Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Harry Potters cousin who often teases and bullies him?",
        "correct_answer": " Dudley",
        "answer_a": " Malfoy",
        "answer_b": " Hagrid",
        "answer_c": " Dudley",
        "answer_d": " Ronald"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first name of Harry Potters mother?",
        "correct_answer": " Lily",
        "answer_a": " Pearl",
        "answer_b": " Hermione",
        "answer_c": " Lily",
        "answer_d": " Angel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Professor McGonagall teaches Transfiguration at the fictional Hogwarts school.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "The name of Harry Potters owl is Fawkes.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Ronald Weasleys younger sister in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " Ginny",
        "answer_a": " Hermione",
        "answer_b": " Ginny",
        "answer_c": " Penelope",
        "answer_d": " Petunia"
    },
    {
        "question": "This professor dislikes Harry Potter and unfairly punishes him while favouring Slytherin students.",
        "correct_answer": " Professor Snape",
        "answer_a": " Professor Sprout",
        "answer_b": " Professor Snape",
        "answer_c": " Professor Dumbledore",
        "answer_d": " Professor McGonagall"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the Hogwarts house where Harry Potter stayed?",
        "correct_answer": " Gryffindor",
        "answer_a": " Slytherin",
        "answer_b": " Gryffindor",
        "answer_c": " Ravenclaw",
        "answer_d": " Hufflepuffs"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the names of the famous Weasley twins in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Fred and George",
        "answer_a": " Mary and Maria",
        "answer_b": " Al and Ron",
        "answer_c": " Fred and George",
        "answer_d": " Arthur and Artlene"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter was the seeker of Gryffindors Quidditch Team.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the hippogriff that hurt Draco Malfoy in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " Buckbeak",
        "answer_a": " Norbert",
        "answer_b": " Buckbeak",
        "answer_c": " Twinky",
        "answer_d": " Aragon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " J. K. Rowling",
        "answer_a": " Judy Blum",
        "answer_b": " J. K. Rowling",
        "answer_c": " E. B. White",
        "answer_d": " J. R. Rowling"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the form into which Harry Potters godfather transforms in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " A dog",
        "answer_a": " A dog",
        "answer_b": " A snake",
        "answer_c": " A bird",
        "answer_d": " A cat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the new Defence Against the Dark Arts teacher who first appears in the novel Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " Professor Lupin",
        "answer_a": " Professor Lupin",
        "answer_b": " Professor Moody",
        "answer_c": " Professor Binns",
        "answer_d": " Professor Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did the Defence Against the Dark Arts professor teach Harry after the quidditch match in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " The Patronus Charm",
        "answer_a": " A way to become invisible",
        "answer_b": " How to get rid of a boggart",
        "answer_c": " How to sleep without any dreams",
        "answer_d": " The Patronus Charm"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does Harry Potter go to Hogsmede in the third book of the series?",
        "correct_answer": " He uses the marauders map and his invisibility cloak.",
        "answer_a": " He uses the marauders invisible cloak.",
        "answer_b": " None of these",
        "answer_c": " He uses only the marauders map.",
        "answer_d": " He uses the marauders map and his invisibility cloak."
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, when Snape taught the Defence Against the Dark Arts, what was the subject the class talked and read about?",
        "correct_answer": " Werewolves",
        "answer_a": " Werewolves",
        "answer_b": " Hippogriffs",
        "answer_c": " Mermaids",
        "answer_d": " Boggarts"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the device that Hermione uses to travel back in time in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " Time Turner",
        "answer_a": " Time Turner",
        "answer_b": " Hourglass",
        "answer_c": " Changer of Time",
        "answer_d": " Time Stopper"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do Harry and Hermione go somewhere, without Ron, at the end of the movie Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Andersens fairy tale The Princess and the Pea, a young woman arrives at the royal familys gate and claims to be a real princess. Who decides to test the validity of her claim by placing a pea under her mattresses?",
        "correct_answer": " the Queen",
        "answer_a": " the Queen",
        "answer_b": " the King",
        "answer_c": " the Princes sister",
        "answer_d": " the Prince"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who takes Hansel and Gretel to the forest and abandons them there in Grimms classic fairy tale?",
        "correct_answer": " their father",
        "answer_a": " their father",
        "answer_b": " the with",
        "answer_c": " their stepfather",
        "answer_d": " their mother"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these fairy tales by Danish author Hans Christian Andersen has a happy ending?",
        "correct_answer": " The Snow Queen",
        "answer_a": " The Snow Queen",
        "answer_b": " All of these",
        "answer_c": " The Little Match Girl",
        "answer_d": " The Little Mermaid"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what fairy tale does a curious wife find the dead bodies of her husbands previous wives?",
        "correct_answer": " Bluebeard",
        "answer_a": " Beauty and the Beast",
        "answer_b": " King Thrushbeard",
        "answer_c": " Rumpelstiltskin",
        "answer_d": " Bluebeard"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the fairy tale The Musicians of Bremen, four animals decide to become musicians upon finding that they are no longer useful to their owners. Which of the following is not one of the four animals?",
        "correct_answer": " a pig",
        "answer_a": " a pig",
        "answer_b": " a rooster",
        "answer_c": " a cat",
        "answer_d": " a donkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which magic object is not correctly matched with the fairy tale?",
        "correct_answer": " The Little Mermaid - a key with drops of blood on it",
        "answer_a": " Aladdin - a lamp",
        "answer_b": " The Little Mermaid - a key with drops of blood on it",
        "answer_c": " Snow White  - a mirror",
        "answer_d": " The Wild Swans - nettle shirts"
    },
    {
        "question": "What popular fairy tale is not a recorded folktale, but an original work?",
        "correct_answer": " The Emperors New Clothes",
        "answer_a": " Rapunzel",
        "answer_b": " Sleeping Beauty",
        "answer_c": " The Emperors New Clothes",
        "answer_d": " The Wolf and the Seven Young Kids"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does Belle have to live in the castle with the Beast in the fairy tale The Beauty and the Beast?",
        "correct_answer": " because her father picked up a flower from the Beasts garden",
        "answer_a": " because she picked up a flower from the Beasts garden",
        "answer_b": " because her sisters have stolen an enchanted mirror and a ring from the Beast",
        "answer_c": " because her father picked up a flower from the Beasts garden",
        "answer_d": " because her sisters have stolen jewelry from the Beast"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the names of the Princess and the Prince in the 1959 Disney animated feature, based on Charles Perrault classic tale Sleeping Beauty?",
        "correct_answer": " Aurora and Philip",
        "answer_a": " The Princess is named Aurora, the Prince is anonymous.",
        "answer_b": " Briar-Rose and Stefan",
        "answer_c": " Aurora and Philip",
        "answer_d": " They are anonymous."
    },
    {
        "question": "What diminutive fairy tale character encounters a toad, a beetle, a mouse, a mole and a swallow?",
        "correct_answer": " Thumbelina",
        "answer_a": " Tom Thumb",
        "answer_b": " The Steadfast Tin Soldier",
        "answer_c": " Hop o My Thumb",
        "answer_d": " Thumbelina"
    },
    {
        "question": "Joe has 20 apples. He gave 2 away to a friend and then he ate one. How many apples did he have after that?",
        "correct_answer": " 17",
        "answer_a": " 20",
        "answer_b": " 17",
        "answer_c": " 19",
        "answer_d": " 16"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does x equal in this equation?",
        "correct_answer": " 2",
        "answer_a": " 8",
        "answer_b": " 2",
        "answer_c": " 6",
        "answer_d": " 4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Can 37 be divided into 2 evenly?",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the answer to the following:",
        "correct_answer": " 5",
        "answer_a": " 5",
        "answer_b": " 0",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 2"
    },
    {
        "question": "The reciprocal of 3/4 is 1 1/3.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the square root of 121?",
        "correct_answer": " 11",
        "answer_a": " 10",
        "answer_b": " 11",
        "answer_c": " 12",
        "answer_d": " 13"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is this correct?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "One angle in a triangle is 47 degrees and the second angle is 106 degrees. How many degrees are in the third angle?",
        "correct_answer": " 27",
        "answer_a": " 37",
        "answer_b": " 27",
        "answer_c": " 207",
        "answer_d": " 17"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the missing number?",
        "correct_answer": " 16",
        "answer_a": " 16",
        "answer_b": " 17",
        "answer_c": " 15",
        "answer_d": " 14"
    },
    {
        "question": "You have a right-angled triangle. You know that one leg is 3 cm long and the second leg is 4 cm long. What is the length of the hypotenuse of that triangle?",
        "correct_answer": " 5",
        "answer_a": " 4",
        "answer_b": " 5",
        "answer_c": " 7",
        "answer_d": " 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Founded in 1607, this was the first successful English settlement in what is now the United States.",
        "correct_answer": " Jamestown in present day Virginia",
        "answer_a": " Jamestown in present day Virginia",
        "answer_b": " Boston in present day Massachusetts",
        "answer_c": " Providence in what is present day Rhode Island",
        "answer_d": " Charlestown in present day South Carolina"
    },
    {
        "question": "Up until 1763, the English and this other European nation fought a series of wars and smaller conflicts to see who would dominate what is now the US and Canada.",
        "correct_answer": " France",
        "answer_a": " Holland",
        "answer_b": " France",
        "answer_c": " Germany",
        "answer_d": " Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the biggest issue that eventually led to the English colonies rebellion against their mother country and sparked the American Revolutionary War?",
        "correct_answer": " whether the English Parliament or colonial assemblies would control taxes in the colonies",
        "answer_a": " whether the English Parliament or colonial assemblies would control taxes in the colonies",
        "answer_b": " religious differences between American colonists and Britain",
        "answer_c": " restrictions on the number of English persons who could move to the English colonies",
        "answer_d": " disagreements between Parliament and the colonies over relations with the Native Americans (Indians)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these statements about George Washington is true?",
        "correct_answer": " all of these",
        "answer_a": " all of these",
        "answer_b": " He was the first president of the United States.",
        "answer_c": " He was a successful Virginia plantation owner.",
        "answer_d": " He was commander of the American Continental Army during the Revolutionary War."
    },
    {
        "question": "The final victory in the American Revolutionary War which convinced the British to grant independence to their former colonies was a victory won by combined French and American forces at this place.",
        "correct_answer": " Yorktown",
        "answer_a": " Yorktown",
        "answer_b": " Lexington",
        "answer_c": " Boston",
        "answer_d": " Saratoga"
    },
    {
        "question": "The seventh president of the United States was the first US president elected from a state west of the Appalachian Mountains (Tennessee). He was also the leader of the US forces who gained a major victory over the British at New Orleans in the War of 1812. Who was he?",
        "correct_answer": " Andrew Jackson",
        "answer_a": " James Polk",
        "answer_b": " Andrew Jackson",
        "answer_c": " Thomas Jefferson",
        "answer_d": " John Adams"
    },
    {
        "question": "As a result of victory in the Mexican War of 1846-48, the United States gained all of the following states EXCEPT this one.",
        "correct_answer": " Oregon",
        "answer_a": " Oregon",
        "answer_b": " Arizona",
        "answer_c": " California",
        "answer_d": " Nevada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the one irreconcilable issue between North and South that led to the American Civil War?",
        "correct_answer": " slavery",
        "answer_a": " slavery",
        "answer_b": " status of new western territories",
        "answer_c": " states rights",
        "answer_d": " tariffs"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Union victory in this battle, fought in July 1863, is generally considered the turning point of the American Civil War. After the battle President Lincoln made a memorable speech at the site of the battle. What was the battle?",
        "correct_answer": " Gettysburg",
        "answer_a": " Gettysburg",
        "answer_b": " Shiloh",
        "answer_c": " Second Bull Run",
        "answer_d": " Antietam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is true about the United States in the period between the end of the Civil War in 1865 and the beginning of the 20th century?",
        "correct_answer": " US industrialization advanced rapidly.",
        "answer_a": " Blacks in the southern states were integrated into the southern population with very little conflict or discrimination.",
        "answer_b": " Native Americans (Indians) were generally treated fairly and territorial disputes were settled.",
        "answer_c": " US industrialization advanced rapidly.",
        "answer_d": " Laws were passed that greatly restricted European immigration into the US."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following was NOT a reason why the US entered World War One on the side of Britain and France?",
        "correct_answer": " President Wilson wanted to destroy communism.",
        "answer_a": " German submarines began sinking US ships in 1917.",
        "answer_b": " The US had strong cultural and commercial ties with Britain and France.",
        "answer_c": " France and Britain were democratic and Germany was not.",
        "answer_d": " President Wilson wanted to destroy communism."
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1919 an amendment to the US Constitution (which was rescinded in 1933) prohibited which of the following?",
        "correct_answer": " alcoholic beverages",
        "answer_a": " US joining any international organization",
        "answer_b": " alcoholic beverages",
        "answer_c": " prostitution",
        "answer_d": " same sex marriages"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1933 Franklin Roosevelt was elected president. He promised to bring a New Deal to Americans to bring recovery from the Great Depression and improve social conditions. Which of the following did his New Deal include?",
        "correct_answer": " All of these",
        "answer_a": " Programs to provide jobs by building roads, schools, dams, etc.",
        "answer_b": " The Securities and Exchange Commission to regulate the stock market",
        "answer_c": " Social Security that provided pensions for retired workers",
        "answer_d": " All of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Japanese defeat in this naval battle in the Pacific is generally considered to be the turning point of the Second World War.",
        "correct_answer": " Midway",
        "answer_a": " Leyte Gulf",
        "answer_b": " Okinawa",
        "answer_c": " Singapore",
        "answer_d": " Midway"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these statements is NOT true about the Cold War?",
        "correct_answer": " There was never any actual warfare in the Cold War.",
        "answer_a": " There was never any actual warfare in the Cold War.",
        "answer_b": " It was partly a clash of very different ideologies.",
        "answer_c": " It began soon after World War Two ended, partly because of Soviet domination of Eastern Europe.",
        "answer_d": " Nuclear weapons were a threat to both sides in the Cold War."
    },
    {
        "question": "Many think that the closest the world came to nuclear war was in 1962 when President Kennedy demanded that the Soviets remove nuclear missiles they had recently placed in this country.",
        "correct_answer": " Cuba",
        "answer_a": " Germany",
        "answer_b": " North Korea",
        "answer_c": " China",
        "answer_d": " Cuba"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ole Kirk Christiansen, the founder of the LEGO Group, started producing wooden toys in what year?",
        "correct_answer": " 1932",
        "answer_a": " 1939",
        "answer_b": " 1932",
        "answer_c": " 1934",
        "answer_d": " 1927"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1934, Ole Kirk Christiansen named his toy-producing company LEGO, a word derived from the Danish phrase leg godt, which means what in English?",
        "correct_answer": " Play Well",
        "answer_a": " Put Together",
        "answer_b": " Play Well",
        "answer_c": " Build Well",
        "answer_d": " Stack Well"
    },
    {
        "question": "During this year the Lego company, founded by Ole Kirk Christiansen, was devastated by a fire.",
        "correct_answer": " 1942",
        "answer_a": " 1945",
        "answer_b": " 1944",
        "answer_c": " 1942",
        "answer_d": " 1940"
    },
    {
        "question": "LEGO was the first company in Denmark to buy and use a plastic injection-molding machine for toys.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year did Godtfred Kirk Christiansen become Junior Vice President of the LEGO company?",
        "correct_answer": " 1950",
        "answer_a": " 1952",
        "answer_b": " 1949",
        "answer_c": " 1950",
        "answer_d": " 1947"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the revolutionary LEGO series of 28 sets and 8 vehicles, launched in 1955?",
        "correct_answer": " LEGO System of Play",
        "answer_a": " LEGO Building Set",
        "answer_b": " LEGO Toy Set of Building",
        "answer_c": " LEGO System of Play",
        "answer_d": " LEGO System"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1963, the LEGO company replaced the building substance for the bricks, cellulose acetate with acrylonitrile butadiene stryrene, which improved the color quality.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1989, the LEGO company released a new series, named Pirates.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which house of Hogwarts was fictional character Sirius Black in when he attended the famous school?",
        "correct_answer": " Gryffindor",
        "answer_a": " Ravenclaw",
        "answer_b": " Gryffindor",
        "answer_c": " Slytherin",
        "answer_d": " Hufflepuff"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter character Sirius Black was an Animagi meaning that he could take the form of an animal. What animal could he emulate?",
        "correct_answer": " A dog",
        "answer_a": " A wolf",
        "answer_b": " A dog",
        "answer_c": " A Deer",
        "answer_d": " A Rat"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix the headquarters of the organization was in Sirius family home.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which Harry Potter novel did Sirius Black make his first major appearance?",
        "correct_answer": " Harry Potter and The Prisoner of Azkaban",
        "answer_a": " Harry Potter and The Sorcerers Stone",
        "answer_b": " Harry Potter and The Prisoner of Azkaban",
        "answer_c": " Harry potter and The Chamber of Secrets",
        "answer_d": " Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows"
    },
    {
        "question": "What magical flying item of Sirius Black was given to Hagrid upon the knowledge of Harry Potters parents death?",
        "correct_answer": " A motorcycle",
        "answer_a": " A broomstick",
        "answer_b": " A motorcycle",
        "answer_c": " A Car",
        "answer_d": " A carpet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Sirius Blacks father in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Orion",
        "answer_a": " Orion",
        "answer_b": " Teodor",
        "answer_c": " Draco",
        "answer_d": " Rudolph"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sirius Black dies in the novel Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following classes was taught by Professor Snape in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Potions",
        "answer_a": " Divination",
        "answer_b": " Potions",
        "answer_c": " Charms",
        "answer_d": " Astronomy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What secret about Professor Snape was divulged in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, which is the final book in the series?",
        "correct_answer": " He was in love with Harrys mother.",
        "answer_a": " He was half muggle.",
        "answer_b": " He killed Albus Dumbledore.",
        "answer_c": " He was in love with Harrys mother.",
        "answer_d": " He was Lord Voldemorts brother."
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter series, Professor Snape became headmaster of Hogwarts after the death of Dumbledore.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Snapes patronus in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Doe",
        "answer_a": " Doe",
        "answer_b": " Dragon",
        "answer_c": " Wolf",
        "answer_d": " Snake"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the final book of the Harry Potter series, Harry finally kills Snape.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter series, what was the teaching position most coveted by Professor Snape?",
        "correct_answer": " Defense Against the Dark Arts",
        "answer_a": " Care of magical Creatures",
        "answer_b": " Potions",
        "answer_c": " Divination",
        "answer_d": " Defense Against the Dark Arts"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the final book in the Harry Potter series, it is revealed that Harry names one of his sons after Snape.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is fictional character Snape the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Mr. Crouch from the Ministry of Magic call Percy in book 4 of the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Weatherby",
        "answer_a": " Rainlet",
        "answer_b": " Cloudy boy",
        "answer_c": " Weatherboy",
        "answer_d": " Weatherby"
    },
    {
        "question": "There were all types of enchantments guarding the Sorcerers Stone. Which teacher put the flying keys there to protect it in the first Harry Potter book?",
        "correct_answer": " Professor Flitwick",
        "answer_a": " Professor Snape",
        "answer_b": " Professor Sprout",
        "answer_c": " Professor Quirrell",
        "answer_d": " Professor Flitwick"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which two books did Harry Potter make a Patronus because he thought he saw a dementor, even though it was not really a dementor?",
        "correct_answer": " Books 3 and 4",
        "answer_a": " Books 3 and 5",
        "answer_b": " Books 3 and 4",
        "answer_c": " Books 4 and 5",
        "answer_d": " Books 3 and 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the sixth book of the Harry Potter series, Professor Slughorn became the Head of Slytherin.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "The character of Sirius Black is mentioned in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban for the first time.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Harry Potter characters is not a prefect?",
        "correct_answer": " Harry Potter",
        "answer_a": " Tom Riddle",
        "answer_b": " Harry Potter",
        "answer_c": " Pansy Parkinson",
        "answer_d": " Ron Weasley"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these characters does Harry kiss in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Ginny",
        "answer_a": " Cho",
        "answer_b": " No one",
        "answer_c": " Ginny",
        "answer_d": " Hermione"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lavender Brown and Ron Won Won Weasley start going out in chapter 9 of Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What previously mentioned character was killed in chapter 1 of Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Amelia Bones",
        "answer_a": " Kingsley Shackelbolt",
        "answer_b": " Stubby Boardman",
        "answer_c": " Percival Wulfricshire",
        "answer_d": " Amelia Bones"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, Cho Chang waves to Harry once but then hurries away with Marietta.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Merope supposedly use to make Tom Riddle Sr. fall in love with her in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " A love potion",
        "answer_a": " A love potion",
        "answer_b": " A love spell",
        "answer_c": " An imperious curse",
        "answer_d": " A potion and spell"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, is Dumbledores blood the only blood used in the Cavern by the sea where the Horcrux is hidden?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, a corpse that is re-animated but isn\u2019t alive is called what?",
        "correct_answer": " Inferi",
        "answer_a": " Inferi",
        "answer_b": " Infery",
        "answer_c": " Infreri",
        "answer_d": " Infrery"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry destroyed two Horcruxes in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lord Voldemort had the ability to talk to these creatures.",
        "correct_answer": " Snakes",
        "answer_a": " Snakes",
        "answer_b": " Wolves",
        "answer_c": " Spiders",
        "answer_d": " Centaurs"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Lord Voldemorts real first name?",
        "correct_answer": " Tom",
        "answer_a": " John",
        "answer_b": " Michael",
        "answer_c": " Tom",
        "answer_d": " Ron"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the very first of Lord Voldemorts horcruxes to appear in the Harry Potter series of books?",
        "correct_answer": " Diary",
        "answer_a": " Sword",
        "answer_b": " Stone",
        "answer_c": " Diary",
        "answer_d": " Ring"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these Hogwarts founders was Lord Voldemorts ancestor?",
        "correct_answer": " Slytherin",
        "answer_a": " Ravenclaw",
        "answer_b": " Huffelpuff",
        "answer_c": " Slytherin",
        "answer_d": " Gryffendore"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lord Voldemort is related to Harry Potter.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these characters does Voldemort NOT kill in the final Harry Potter book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " Hagrid",
        "answer_a": " Tonks",
        "answer_b": " Severus Snape",
        "answer_c": " Hagrid",
        "answer_d": " Professor Lupin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter defeats and kills Lord Voldemort in the final Harry Potter book.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What childrens novel features Neverland, the magical island where people cease to age?",
        "correct_answer": " Peter and Wendy",
        "answer_a": " Alices Adventures in Wonderland",
        "answer_b": " Peter and Wendy",
        "answer_c": " Pinocchio",
        "answer_d": " Pippi Longstocking"
    },
    {
        "question": "What classic fictional character is a long-nosed wooden puppet?",
        "correct_answer": " Both of these",
        "answer_a": " Both of these",
        "answer_b": " Pinocchio",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " Buratino"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a character from Lewis Carrolls 1865 novel Alices Adventures in Wonderland?",
        "correct_answer": " the Chief Weasel",
        "answer_a": " the Queen of Hearts",
        "answer_b": " the Mock Turtle",
        "answer_c": " the March Hare",
        "answer_d": " the Chief Weasel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What character from Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9rys novella, The Little Prince, utters these famous lines that sum up the essence of the book: One cannot see well except with the heart, the essential is invisible to the eyes.?",
        "correct_answer": " the Fox",
        "answer_a": " the Fox",
        "answer_b": " the Snake",
        "answer_c": " the Lamplighter",
        "answer_d": " the Rose"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the birth name of the author who penned The English Roses, a childrens book that follows the lives of four girls?",
        "correct_answer": " Madonna Louise Ciccone",
        "answer_a": " Theodor Seuss Geisel",
        "answer_b": " Helen Beatrix Potter",
        "answer_c": " Madonna Louise Ciccone",
        "answer_d": " Dorothy Gladys Smith"
    },
    {
        "question": "What childrens book author named one of his central characters after his son?",
        "correct_answer": " A. A. Milne",
        "answer_a": " C. S. Lewis",
        "answer_b": " Lemony Snicket",
        "answer_c": " A. A. Milne",
        "answer_d": " Lewis Carroll"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these Disney animated features is not based on a book written by an European author?",
        "correct_answer": " Mulan",
        "answer_a": " One Hundred and One Dalmatians",
        "answer_b": " The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh",
        "answer_c": " Mulan",
        "answer_d": " Bambi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What best-selling novel tells the story of an orphan girl adopted by middle-aged siblings, Marilla and Matthew Cuthbert?",
        "correct_answer": " Anne of Green Gables",
        "answer_a": " Little House in the Big Woods",
        "answer_b": " Anne of Green Gables",
        "answer_c": " Little Women",
        "answer_d": " Heidi"
    },
    {
        "question": "This extraordinary strong, red-haired fictional character lives in Villa Villekula with a monkey, named Mr. Nilsson.",
        "correct_answer": " Pippi",
        "answer_a": " Karlsson",
        "answer_b": " Pippi",
        "answer_c": " Ronia",
        "answer_d": " Lucy Pevensie"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which characters are not correctly matched with the authors who created them?",
        "correct_answer": " Mowgly, Raksha - Edgar Rice Burroughs",
        "answer_a": " Lucy Pevensie, Caspian - C. S. Lewis",
        "answer_b": " Mowgly, Raksha - Edgar Rice Burroughs",
        "answer_c": " Joe Harper, Becky Thatcher  - Mark Twain",
        "answer_d": " Meg March, Amy March - Louisa May Alcott"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Severus Snape was headmaster for a period of time.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the first chapter of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, why was Snape late for a meeting with Lord Voldemort?",
        "correct_answer": " He discovered something important.",
        "answer_a": " He discovered something important.",
        "answer_b": " He forgot what time it was.",
        "answer_c": " He does not like meetings.",
        "answer_d": " He was teaching."
    },
    {
        "question": "The first sentence in the second chapter in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows is Harry was bleeding. Why is that so?",
        "correct_answer": " Harry got cut by a fragment of a mirror.",
        "answer_a": " Harry got cut by a fragment of a mirror.",
        "answer_b": " Dudley put a cup of tea right behind Harrys door and Harry stepped on it.",
        "answer_c": " Dudley put a glass of water behind Harrys door and Harry stepped on it.",
        "answer_d": " Harry bit his lip."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Deathly Hallow?",
        "correct_answer": " Magical Mirror",
        "answer_a": " Resurrection Stone",
        "answer_b": " Magical Mirror",
        "answer_c": " Elder Wand",
        "answer_d": " Invisibility Cloak"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Weasley boy got his ear cut off in the last book of the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " George",
        "answer_a": " Ron",
        "answer_b": " Fred",
        "answer_c": " Bill",
        "answer_d": " George"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Harry Potter say that his name was when he, Ron, and Hermione got caught by a gang of Snatchers in Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " Vernon Dudley",
        "answer_a": " Dudley Dursley",
        "answer_b": " Vernon Dursley",
        "answer_c": " Dudley Vernon",
        "answer_d": " Vernon Dudley"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you add 3 to 5, what would be the result?",
        "correct_answer": " 8",
        "answer_a": " 6",
        "answer_b": " 8",
        "answer_c": " 5",
        "answer_d": " 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "If Jane had $3.00 and went to the store and bought a yo yo for $1.00, how much would Jane have left?",
        "correct_answer": " $2.00",
        "answer_a": " $2.25",
        "answer_b": " $1.50",
        "answer_c": " $1.00",
        "answer_d": " $2.00"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct solution to this problem: 16 - 4 + 3 =?",
        "correct_answer": " 15",
        "answer_a": " 14",
        "answer_b": " 15",
        "answer_c": " 13",
        "answer_d": " 16"
    },
    {
        "question": "If T.J. went to the circus with 10 dollars and bought some fruit snacks for 3 dollars, how much money would T. J. then have left over?",
        "correct_answer": " 7 dollars",
        "answer_a": " 8 dollars",
        "answer_b": " 3 dollars",
        "answer_c": " 7 dollars",
        "answer_d": " 5 dollars"
    },
    {
        "question": "If Lindsay had $20.00 and bought 3 tickets to the Mets game, how much money would Lindsay have left if each ticket cost 5 dollars?",
        "correct_answer": " 5 dollars",
        "answer_a": " 5 dollars",
        "answer_b": " 10 dollars",
        "answer_c": " 8 dollars",
        "answer_d": " 15 dollars"
    },
    {
        "question": "If Donna bought 5 blowpop lollipops from the candy store and gave her friend 2 of them, how many blowpops would Donna then have?",
        "correct_answer": " 3",
        "answer_a": " 3",
        "answer_b": " 4",
        "answer_c": " 2",
        "answer_d": " 1"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many inches are there in a foot?",
        "correct_answer": " 12",
        "answer_a": " 12",
        "answer_b": " 6",
        "answer_c": " 18",
        "answer_d": " 10"
    },
    {
        "question": "If Anthony had 8 apples, 2 oranges and 3 pears, how many pieces of fruit does Anthony have altogether?",
        "correct_answer": " 13",
        "answer_a": " 14",
        "answer_b": " 13",
        "answer_c": " 12",
        "answer_d": " 11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the solution to this problem 12-3=?",
        "correct_answer": " 9",
        "answer_a": " 8",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 7",
        "answer_d": " 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "Amanda went to the book store to buy some books. Her mom gave her a $10 bill. She bought two books that cost $2.00 each and a bookmark that cost $1.00. How much change did Amanda give her mother when she got home?",
        "correct_answer": " 5 dollars",
        "answer_a": " 40 dollars",
        "answer_b": " 6 dollars",
        "answer_c": " 4 dollars",
        "answer_d": " 5 dollars"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did Sirius Black escape from Azkaban, the wizard prison in the third book of the Harry Poter series?",
        "correct_answer": " He transformed into a dog.",
        "answer_a": " None of these",
        "answer_b": " He was able to contact his cousin Bellatrix who helped him escape from Azkaban.",
        "answer_c": " He transformed into a dog.",
        "answer_d": " He was able to control one of the dementors."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher in Harry Potters third year at Hogwarts?",
        "correct_answer": " Remus Lupin",
        "answer_a": " Severus Snape",
        "answer_b": " Remus Lupin",
        "answer_c": " Dolores Umbridge",
        "answer_d": " Alastor Mad-Eye Moody"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional character Remus Lupin was an animagus.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the spell incantation for conjuring a Patronus in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " Expecto Patronum",
        "answer_a": " Expelliarmus",
        "answer_b": " Impedimenta",
        "answer_c": " Wingardium Leviosa",
        "answer_d": " Expecto Patronum"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, Rubeus Hagrid was appointed by Headmaster Albus Dumbledore as the new teacher of what subject?",
        "correct_answer": " Care of Magical Creatures",
        "answer_a": " Care of Magical Creatures",
        "answer_b": " Potions",
        "answer_c": " Transfiguration",
        "answer_d": " Defense Against the Dark Arts"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who gave the Marauders Map to Harry in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
        "correct_answer": " Fred and George",
        "answer_a": " Fred and George",
        "answer_b": " Remus Lupin",
        "answer_c": " Argus Filch",
        "answer_d": " Rubeus Hagrid"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Shrieking Shack, depicted in the Harry Potter books, was considered to be the most haunted place in Great Britain.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Even without a permission slip, Harry Potter was able to go to Hogsmeade with Ron and Hermione during certain weekends.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2000, this Mouseketeer became the youngest person to be both host and musical guest on Saturday Night Live.",
        "correct_answer": " Britney Spears",
        "answer_a": " Nikki DeLoach",
        "answer_b": " Britney Spears",
        "answer_c": " Justin Timberlake",
        "answer_d": " JC Chasez"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the weekly ten-minute drama on the All-New Mickey Mouse Club starring Tony Lucca, Keri Russel and JC Chasez?",
        "correct_answer": " Emerald Cove",
        "answer_a": " The Party",
        "answer_b": " Spin and Marty",
        "answer_c": " Emerald Cove",
        "answer_d": " The Hardy Boys"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, who delivered the Prime Minister the message that the Minister of Magic had sent?",
        "correct_answer": " An oil painting",
        "answer_a": " An oil painting",
        "answer_b": " Amelia Bones",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " Herbert Chorley"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, The Minister of Magic came only once to visit the Prime Minister.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was spattered over the wallpaper on Professor Slughorns house in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Dragon blood",
        "answer_a": " Pumpkin juice",
        "answer_b": " Dragon blood",
        "answer_c": " Dwarf blood",
        "answer_d": " Ink"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the magazine named Quibbler in the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Luna Lovegoods father",
        "answer_a": " Luna Lovegood",
        "answer_b": " Luna Lovegoods uncle",
        "answer_c": " Ron Weasley",
        "answer_d": " Luna Lovegoods father"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of spell that Harry used on Malfoy in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Sectumsempra",
        "answer_a": " Alohomora",
        "answer_b": " Sectumsempra",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " Felix Felicis"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do Hermione and Ron secretly like each other in the sixth book of the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the sixth book of the Harry Potter series, which of the following characters eventually formed a couple?",
        "correct_answer": " Harry - Ginny",
        "answer_a": " Harry - Ginny",
        "answer_b": " Harry - Hermione",
        "answer_c": " Harry - Cho",
        "answer_d": " None of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color was Quirrels turban in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " purple",
        "answer_a": " blue",
        "answer_b": " purple",
        "answer_c": " red",
        "answer_d": " black"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potters middle name is James.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why was the womping willow planted in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " So Lupin could come to school",
        "answer_a": " So Harry and Ron would have something to run into with the flying car",
        "answer_b": " The students could have shade",
        "answer_c": " So Lupin could come to school",
        "answer_d": " To protect the school"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does Malfoy join the Slytherin quidditch team?",
        "correct_answer": " His father bought brooms for the whole team",
        "answer_a": " He was the only candidate.",
        "answer_b": " He was actually good enough.",
        "answer_c": " His father bought brooms for the whole team",
        "answer_d": " He shot a man in Reno just to watch him die."
    },
    {
        "question": "How is Sirius related to Harry Potter?",
        "correct_answer": " He is Harrys Godfather.",
        "answer_a": " He is Harrys Godfather.",
        "answer_b": " He is Harrys uncle.",
        "answer_c": " He is Harrys cousin.",
        "answer_d": " He is Harrys half-brother."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the teacher in the Harry Potter books that is made fun of by the Marauders map?",
        "correct_answer": " Snape",
        "answer_a": " Lupin",
        "answer_b": " Trelawny",
        "answer_c": " McGonagall",
        "answer_d": " Snape"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who wrote the Harry Potter series of books?",
        "correct_answer": " J.K. Rowling",
        "answer_a": " J.R. Rowling",
        "answer_b": " C.S. Lewis",
        "answer_c": " J.K. Rowling",
        "answer_d": " J.R. Tolkien"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were Hermiones and Chos patronus forms in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " Swan and Otter",
        "answer_a": " Swan and Otter",
        "answer_b": " Stag and Frog",
        "answer_c": " Frog and Otter",
        "answer_d": " Frog and Swan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional characters Ron Weasley and Harry Potter met on the Hogwarts Express.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Every headmaster/headmistress of the fictional Hogwarts school has had the same office.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What magical object did Harry Potter use to save Ron from poisoning?",
        "correct_answer": " bezoar",
        "answer_a": " antidote to love potions",
        "answer_b": " wand",
        "answer_c": " bezoar",
        "answer_d": " boggart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional character Mr. Weasley was on guard duty when the basilisk attacked him.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does fictional character Ron Weasley live at 12, Grimmauld Place?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what Harry Potter book did the Brockdale Bridge collapse?",
        "correct_answer": " Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
        "answer_a": " Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
        "answer_b": " Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix.",
        "answer_c": " Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban",
        "answer_d": " Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional characters Fred and George Weasley get kicked out of Hogwarts.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Headmaster at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in books 1-6 of the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Albus Dumbledore",
        "answer_a": " Phineas Nigeallus",
        "answer_b": " Minevera McGonagall",
        "answer_c": " Severus Snape",
        "answer_d": " Albus Dumbledore"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is head of the fictional Gryffindor house?",
        "correct_answer": " McGonagall",
        "answer_a": " Snape",
        "answer_b": " McGonagall",
        "answer_c": " Lupin",
        "answer_d": " Trelawney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional character Professor Snape is head of Ravenclaw house.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Flitwick head of Huffllepuff house in the Harry Potter series of books?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is head of Slytherin house in the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " Slughorn",
        "answer_a": " Slughorn",
        "answer_b": " McGonagal",
        "answer_c": " Sprout",
        "answer_d": " Snape"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the ghost of Ravenclaw in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " The Gray Lady",
        "answer_a": " Sprout",
        "answer_b": " The Bloody Baron",
        "answer_c": " The Gray Lady",
        "answer_d": " Flitwick"
    },
    {
        "question": "Professor Sprout is head of Hufflepuff, one of the fictional Hogwarts houses.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Gryffindor ghost in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " Nearly Headless Nick",
        "answer_a": " Moaning Myrtle",
        "answer_b": " The Gray Lady",
        "answer_c": " The Bloody Baron",
        "answer_d": " Nearly Headless Nick"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter books, the Bloody Baron is Slytherins ghost.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Harry Potter a member of Gryffindor house?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the square root of 144?",
        "correct_answer": " 12",
        "answer_a": " 12",
        "answer_b": " 7",
        "answer_c": " 14",
        "answer_d": " 71"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the first book of the Harry Potter series, when Harry, Ron and Hermione went into the restricted corridor, what was the order of the obstacles to get to Quirrell?",
        "correct_answer": " Devils Snare, keys, chessboard, potions",
        "answer_a": " Keys, Devils Snare, chessboard, potions",
        "answer_b": " Chessboard, keys, Devils Snare, potions",
        "answer_c": " Devils Snare, chessboard, keys, potions",
        "answer_d": " Devils Snare, keys, chessboard, potions"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shape does Sirius Blacks Animagus take in the 3rd book of the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " a black dog",
        "answer_a": " a Dachshund",
        "answer_b": " a black dog",
        "answer_c": " a black cat",
        "answer_d": " a yellow cat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the address of the Order of the Phoenix headquarters in the Harry Potter novels?",
        "correct_answer": " number 12, Grimmauld place",
        "answer_a": " number 19, Grimmauld place",
        "answer_b": " number 15, Grimmauld place",
        "answer_c": " number 13, Grimmauld place",
        "answer_d": " number 12, Grimmauld place"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where did fictional character Tom Riddle (Voldemort) live before going to live and study at Hogwarts?",
        "correct_answer": " an orphanage",
        "answer_a": " an ordinary house",
        "answer_b": " an run-down shack",
        "answer_c": " a school bus",
        "answer_d": " an orphanage"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people died at the fictional battle of Hogwarts?",
        "correct_answer": " 54",
        "answer_a": " 51",
        "answer_b": " 53",
        "answer_c": " 54",
        "answer_d": " 55"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did Harry Potter marry Ginny Weasley?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "All the books of the Harry Potter series are set in England and Scotland.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many champions names came out of the fictional Goblet of Fire?",
        "correct_answer": " 4",
        "answer_a": " 1",
        "answer_b": " 3",
        "answer_c": " 2",
        "answer_d": " 4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first guardian to whom the Baudelaires were sent in A Series of Unfortunate Events?",
        "correct_answer": " Count Olaf",
        "answer_a": " Madam Lulu.",
        "answer_b": " Aunt Josephine",
        "answer_c": " Esme Squalor",
        "answer_d": " Count Olaf"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the novel The Penultimate Peril, Jaques Snicket was one of the two people who signed into the hotel as J.S..",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character from A Series of Unfortunate Events said that orphans were in?",
        "correct_answer": " Esme Squalor",
        "answer_a": " Hector",
        "answer_b": " Jerome Squalor",
        "answer_c": " Uncle Monty",
        "answer_d": " Esme Squalor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following were mentioned in the book The Ersatz Elevator?",
        "correct_answer": " The King of Arizona",
        "answer_a": " The King of Arizona",
        "answer_b": " The President of Nepal",
        "answer_c": " The Prime Minister of New York",
        "answer_d": " The Grand Admiral of Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following fictional characters, depicted by Lemony Snicket, is a poet?",
        "correct_answer": " Isadora Quagmire",
        "answer_a": " Uncle Monty",
        "answer_b": " Duncan Quagmire",
        "answer_c": " Kit Snicket",
        "answer_d": " Isadora Quagmire"
    },
    {
        "question": "In A Series of Unfortunate Events, whose head was always hidden behind a cloud of smoke?",
        "correct_answer": " Sirs",
        "answer_a": " Phils",
        "answer_b": " Beatrices",
        "answer_c": " Carmelita Spats",
        "answer_d": " Sirs"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the second book of A Series of Unfortunate Events, did Count Olaf trick the Baudelaires into thinking he was really Stephano?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which of Lemony Snickets books does Jaques Snicket die?",
        "correct_answer": " The Vile Village",
        "answer_a": " The Miserable Mill",
        "answer_b": " The Bad Beginning",
        "answer_c": " The Vile Village",
        "answer_d": " The Penultimate Peril"
    },
    {
        "question": "In A Series of Unfortunate Events, Klaus was the best inventor out of all the Baudelaires.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "This character is in a show with his two friends, Widget and Walden. He is yellow with a long, springy tail, and greets people by saying, Wow wow.",
        "correct_answer": " Wubbzy",
        "answer_a": " Willard",
        "answer_b": " Wanker",
        "answer_c": " Hank",
        "answer_d": " Wubbzy"
    },
    {
        "question": "The show Dora the Explorer features a little girl who goes on all sorts of adventures with her friend, Tico the Dog.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "This show features characters with offbeat names like Muno, Foofa, Brobee, Toodee, Plex, and DJ Lance.",
        "correct_answer": " Yo Gabba Gabba!",
        "answer_a": " Yo Pinky Dinky!",
        "answer_b": " Yo Diddle Diddle",
        "answer_c": " Yo Mama Jama",
        "answer_d": " Yo Gabba Gabba!"
    },
    {
        "question": "A TV show that debuted in 2002 features 2 bunnies. Max is a 3 year-old bunny that is always doing something to distract his sister, although he always manages to help her in the end. What is his sisters name?",
        "correct_answer": " Ruby",
        "answer_a": " Pearl",
        "answer_b": " Fluff",
        "answer_c": " Louise",
        "answer_d": " Ruby"
    },
    {
        "question": "This show features an active hero named Sportacus, who uses exercise and good nutrition to thwart the schemes of the slothful Robbie Rotten. Most of the characters in this show are puppets.",
        "correct_answer": " Lazy Town",
        "answer_a": " Sleepy Town",
        "answer_b": " Lazy Town",
        "answer_c": " Active Town",
        "answer_d": " Funky Town"
    },
    {
        "question": "The show Blues Clues featured 2 different hosts during its run. What were their names?",
        "correct_answer": " Steve and Joe",
        "answer_a": " Stan and Stu",
        "answer_b": " Steve and Joe",
        "answer_c": " Larry and Jake",
        "answer_d": " Jack and Jim"
    },
    {
        "question": "This show follows Pablo the Penguin, Tyrone the Moose, Tasha the Hippopotamus, Austin the Kangaroo, and Uniqua on their imaginary adventures in the backyard.",
        "correct_answer": " The Backyardigans",
        "answer_a": " The Backyardamals",
        "answer_b": " The Backyardigans",
        "answer_c": " The Backyard Gang",
        "answer_d": " The Backyard Band"
    },
    {
        "question": "This show centers around a young girl, who speaks English and Chinese, and teaches problem solving. Other characters featured on the show are the girls grandfather,  Ye Ye, and her friends Rintoo, Tolee, Hoho, and Lulu.",
        "correct_answer": " Ni Hao, Kai-Lan",
        "answer_a": " Ni Hao, Kai-Lan",
        "answer_b": " Ni Hao, Karen Chau",
        "answer_c": " Ni Hao, Yeoh-La",
        "answer_d": " Ni Hao, Shu-Shu"
    },
    {
        "question": "Linny, Tuck, and Ming MIng too! These schoolhouse animals are always using teamwork to save baby animals in trouble.",
        "correct_answer": " The Wonder Pets",
        "answer_a": " The Teamwork Trio",
        "answer_b": " The Super Squirrels",
        "answer_c": " The Wonder Pets",
        "answer_d": " The Amazing Animals"
    },
    {
        "question": "This young boy started off in his cousin Dora the Explorers show, but soon received his own show. He is an animal rescuer, along with his sister, Alicia.",
        "correct_answer": " Diego",
        "answer_a": " Marco",
        "answer_b": " Diego",
        "answer_c": " Juan",
        "answer_d": " Luis"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Silver Chair, Eustace Scrubb returns to Narnia with his schoolmate Jill Pole, who attends what school with him?",
        "correct_answer": " Experiment House",
        "answer_a": " Educational High School",
        "answer_b": " Experiment House",
        "answer_c": " English School for Grammar",
        "answer_d": " Experimentation Hall"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens to Eustace as a result of Jills showing off at the edge of the cliff in the book The Silver Chair?",
        "correct_answer": " He looses his balance and falls",
        "answer_a": " Jill gives him a hug",
        "answer_b": " He looses his balance and falls",
        "answer_c": " He is attacked by a lion",
        "answer_d": " Nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the novel The Silver Chair, Aslan gives Jill and Eustace a task and four signs to help them find the way. What is the task?",
        "correct_answer": " To find the Prince Rilian, who has been missing for ten years",
        "answer_a": " To kill the evil Green Witch, who has terrorized Narnia for a decade",
        "answer_b": " To prevent an attack from the underworld upon Narnia",
        "answer_c": " To free the talking beasts of Narnia from the tyranny of the Giants",
        "answer_d": " To find the Prince Rilian, who has been missing for ten years"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first of the signs given to Jill by Aslan in The Silver Chair was that Eustace was to see an old friend. Who did that old friend turn out to be?",
        "correct_answer": " Caspian",
        "answer_a": " Reepicheep",
        "answer_b": " Edmund",
        "answer_c": " Drinian",
        "answer_d": " Caspian"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sort of creature is Glimfeather, who helps Eustace and Jill get started on their journey in The Silver Chair?",
        "correct_answer": " Owl",
        "answer_a": " Parakeet",
        "answer_b": " Gryphon",
        "answer_c": " Owl",
        "answer_d": " Eagle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following statements most correctly describes Puddleglum the Marsh-Wiggles outlook on life in C.S. Lewiss book The Silver Chair?",
        "correct_answer": " He is a pessimist, but is usually proved wrong",
        "answer_a": " He is an optimist and is usually proved wrong",
        "answer_b": " He is an optimist, but is usually proved right",
        "answer_c": " He is a pessimist and is usually proved right",
        "answer_d": " He is a pessimist, but is usually proved wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens to Eustace, Jill and Puddleglum in The Silver Chair, when they knock on the gate of the Giant city of Harfang?",
        "correct_answer": " They are allowed entry and are given food, warm drink and beds.",
        "answer_a": " They are captured by the Giants and thrown into cages.",
        "answer_b": " They are turned away by the Giants that live there and forced to sleep out in the cold.",
        "answer_c": " Nobody answers.",
        "answer_d": " They are allowed entry and are given food, warm drink and beds."
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Silver Chair, Jill has a dream in which she sees what two words out of the window of her room?",
        "correct_answer": " Under Me",
        "answer_a": " Have Faith",
        "answer_b": " Trust Me",
        "answer_c": " Never Surrender",
        "answer_d": " Under Me"
    },
    {
        "question": "When Jill, Eustace and Puddleglum reach the Underworld, in The Silver Chair, they pass a large person sleeping and are told that this is who?",
        "correct_answer": " Father Time",
        "answer_a": " Father Christmas",
        "answer_b": " Father Time",
        "answer_c": " Mother Earth",
        "answer_d": " Mother Nature"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Silver Chair, Prince Rilian is found to be under the enchantment of the Green Witch.  What happens to Rilian for one hour each night under the Witchs spell?",
        "correct_answer": " He remembers who he is and must be tied to a Silver Chair to prevent his escape",
        "answer_a": " He forgets who he is and goes on a murderous rampage",
        "answer_b": " He enters the world of dreams and comes back with ingredients for the Witchs potions",
        "answer_c": " He relives the death of his mother through the eyes of the serpent that killed her",
        "answer_d": " He remembers who he is and must be tied to a Silver Chair to prevent his escape"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Silver Chair, Eustace, Jill and Puddleglum rescue Rilian from the Silver Chair after he begs them to do it in whose name?",
        "correct_answer": " in the name of Aslan",
        "answer_a": " in the name of the White Witch",
        "answer_b": " in the name of God",
        "answer_c": " in the name of Aslan",
        "answer_d": " in the name of the Green Witch"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character in The Silver Chair burns his foot while putting out a magical fire created by the Green Witch?",
        "correct_answer": " Puddleglum",
        "answer_a": " Prince Rilian",
        "answer_b": " Eustace",
        "answer_c": " Jill",
        "answer_d": " Puddleglum"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Silver Chair, Jill and Eustace are allowed the privilege to ride what creature, which is most often too proud to be ridden?",
        "correct_answer": " Centaur",
        "answer_a": " Unicorn",
        "answer_b": " Gryphon",
        "answer_c": " Centaur",
        "answer_d": " Pegasus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which character from the book The Silver Chair accompanies Jill and Eustace back to their own world when Aslan sends them out of his country?",
        "correct_answer": " Caspian",
        "answer_a": " Aslan",
        "answer_b": " Rilian",
        "answer_c": " Caspian",
        "answer_d": " Puddleglum"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the actor who portrayed Harry Potter?",
        "correct_answer": " Daniel Radcliffe",
        "answer_a": " Daniel Fancliff",
        "answer_b": " Daniel Radcliffe",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " Wayne Knight"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cho Chang was Harry Potters girlfriend.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the DADA teacher in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " None of these",
        "answer_a": " Professor Snape",
        "answer_b": " None of these",
        "answer_c": " Professor Lupin",
        "answer_d": " Professor Umbridge"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the anti-Ministry of Magic radio station in Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " Potterwatch",
        "answer_a": " none of these",
        "answer_b": " Potterwatch",
        "answer_c": " The Daily Prophet",
        "answer_d": " The Quibler"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many books are in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " 7",
        "answer_a": " 6",
        "answer_b": " 4",
        "answer_c": " 7",
        "answer_d": " 5"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did Harry Potters parents die on Halloween?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the job of Harry Potters dad?",
        "correct_answer": " He didnt work.",
        "answer_a": " none of these",
        "answer_b": " He didnt work.",
        "answer_c": " minister of magic",
        "answer_d": " quidditch player"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Lucy and Edmund Pevensie return to Narnia along with a boy named Eustace. What relation is Eustace to Lucy and Edmund?",
        "correct_answer": " Cousin",
        "answer_a": " Nephew",
        "answer_b": " Uncle",
        "answer_c": " Cousin",
        "answer_d": " Brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, the three children travel to Narnia by what magical object?",
        "correct_answer": " A painting",
        "answer_a": " A looking glass",
        "answer_b": " A doorway",
        "answer_c": " A painting",
        "answer_d": " A wardrobe"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the third book of the Chronicles of Narnia, the three children are rescued from the sea by Caspian and the crew of the Dawn Treader, who are on a voyage east from Narnia to find what?",
        "correct_answer": " Seven Lords of Narnia banished by Caspians uncle, Miraz",
        "answer_a": " A wife for Caspian to make Queen of Narnia",
        "answer_b": " Queen Susans horn",
        "answer_c": " Seven Lords of Narnia banished by Caspians uncle, Miraz",
        "answer_d": " Five Rings of Power created by Aslan"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the beginning of the voyage, depicted in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Eustace is a nuisance to all aboard the Dawn Treader, including Reepicheep the mouse, whom he greatly offends by doing what?",
        "correct_answer": " Swinging him around by his tail",
        "answer_a": " Kicking him into the water",
        "answer_b": " Stealing his ration of cheese",
        "answer_c": " Swinging him around by his tail",
        "answer_d": " Insulting the honor of his mother"
    },
    {
        "question": "While walking across the island of Felimath, featured in the book The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Caspian, Reepicheep and the three children come across a band of men who they discover to be what?",
        "correct_answer": " Slave Traders",
        "answer_a": " Castaways",
        "answer_b": " Pirates",
        "answer_c": " Ghosts",
        "answer_d": " Slave Traders"
    },
    {
        "question": "What name do the voyagers in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader give to the island on which they find the armor and sword of Lord Restimar lying beside a small pool of clear water?",
        "correct_answer": " Deathwater Island",
        "answer_a": " Tapwater Island",
        "answer_b": " Clearwater Island",
        "answer_c": " Goldwater Island",
        "answer_d": " Deathwater Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Duffers, described in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, have made themselves invisible and wish Lucy to help them become visible again. What was strange about the Duffers?",
        "correct_answer": " They had only one foot",
        "answer_a": " They had only one foot",
        "answer_b": " They had only one eye",
        "answer_c": " They had only one nostril",
        "answer_d": " They had only one hand"
    },
    {
        "question": "As the ship voyages past Magician Coriakins island, the voyagers in the novel The Voyage of the Dawn Treader come across an island surrounded by a shroud of utter darkness. After entering this shroud, what type of animal sheds light to help them escape?",
        "correct_answer": " Albatross",
        "answer_a": " Dolphin",
        "answer_b": " Lion",
        "answer_c": " Lightning Bug",
        "answer_d": " Albatross"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, after rescuing Lord Rhoop, the voyagers land upon another island where they find a large banquet table and three Lords of Narnia, each in an enchanted sleep due to what?",
        "correct_answer": " Touching the stone knife laying on the table",
        "answer_a": " Eating the fruit from the banquet table",
        "answer_b": " Drinking the wine from the flagon on the table",
        "answer_c": " Insulting the daughter of the Lord of the island",
        "answer_d": " Touching the stone knife laying on the table"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sailing past Ramandus island, the voyagers from The Voyage of the Dawn Treader spot a white mass on the horizon. As they approach the white mass, they discover that the sea is covered in what?",
        "correct_answer": " Lilies",
        "answer_a": " Foam",
        "answer_b": " Ice",
        "answer_c": " Frosting",
        "answer_d": " Lilies"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the novel The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, the sea eventually becomes too shallow for the ship to continue and it must turn back, but several members of the crew will continue in the landing boat, hoping to reach Aslans country. On Aslans orders, which of the following characters was made to stay with the Dawn Treader for its return voyage?",
        "correct_answer": " Caspian",
        "answer_a": " Caspian",
        "answer_b": " Eustace",
        "answer_c": " Edmund",
        "answer_d": " Reepicheep"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the house-elf who warned Harry Potter of not going back to school?",
        "correct_answer": " Dobby",
        "answer_a": " Sleepy",
        "answer_b": " Winky",
        "answer_c": " Dizzy",
        "answer_d": " Dobby"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dobby, the house-elf, has been collecting Harry Potters letters to make it seem as though his friends had forgotten him.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry used the Hover Charm to destroy a pudding that Aunt Petunia had made for an important dinner party attended by Uncle Vernons potential client and the clients wife.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, the car which Harry and Ron rode on to Hogwarts, when they werent able to board on Hogwarts Express, crashed into the Whomping Willow.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of Harrys new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " Gilderoy Lockhart",
        "answer_a": " Remus Lupin",
        "answer_b": " Gilderoy Lockhart",
        "answer_c": " Dolores Umbridge",
        "answer_d": " Professor Quirrel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Being the last to go to the barrier between platform 9 and 10 at Kings Cross Station, Harry Potter and Ron were not able to get to platform nine and three-quarters.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you call the fictional language of snakes, according to J. K. Rowlings second book in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Parseltongue",
        "answer_a": " Parsel Language",
        "answer_b": " Basilisks",
        "answer_c": " Snakish",
        "answer_d": " Parseltongue"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did Riddles Magical Diary go into Ginnys hand in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
        "correct_answer": " Lucius Malfoy put it in Ginnys cauldron.",
        "answer_a": " She saw it lying on the floor and took it.",
        "answer_b": " She found it in her trunk.",
        "answer_c": " Lucius Malfoy put it in Ginnys cauldron.",
        "answer_d": " She found it in the girls bathroom at Hogwarts"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry Potter destroyed Riddles Diary with one of the Basilisks poisonous fangs.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter draws a sword from the Sorting Hat during his duel with Tom Riddle and the Basilisk in the Chamber of Secrets. The sword belongs to which of the four founders of Hogwarts houses?",
        "correct_answer": " Godric Gryffindor",
        "answer_a": " Salazar Slytherin",
        "answer_b": " Godric Gryffindor",
        "answer_c": " Helga Hufflepuff",
        "answer_d": " Rowena Ravenclaw"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sort of clothing freed Dobby, the house-elf, from the Malfoys according to the second Harry Potter book?",
        "correct_answer": " a sock",
        "answer_a": " a sock",
        "answer_b": " a hat",
        "answer_c": " a pair of footwear",
        "answer_d": " a new shirt"
    },
    {
        "question": "C.S. Lewis titled his book, Prince Caspian, after the main character, but kept one of his working titles as a subtitle. What is the subtitle of this book?",
        "correct_answer": " Return to Narnia",
        "answer_a": " Return of the King",
        "answer_b": " Aslans Return",
        "answer_c": " Return of Prince Caspian",
        "answer_d": " Return to Narnia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the novel Prince Caspian, what two creatures did the dwarf Nikabrik bring into Prince Caspians counsel in an attempt to convince him to use dark magic against King Miraz?",
        "correct_answer": " A hag and a werewolf",
        "answer_a": " A vampire and an ogre",
        "answer_b": " A werewolf and an ogre",
        "answer_c": " A hag and a werewolf",
        "answer_d": " A hag and a vampire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the Pevensie children first sees Aslan as they journey with the dwarf Trumpkin in the book Prince Caspian?",
        "correct_answer": " Lucy",
        "answer_a": " Lucy",
        "answer_b": " Susan",
        "answer_c": " Peter",
        "answer_d": " Edmund"
    },
    {
        "question": "During the battle between King Miraz and Peter depicted in the book Prince Caspian, which of the following does not happen?",
        "correct_answer": " Aslan stops the battle before anyone is killed.",
        "answer_a": " Miraz is betrayed and killed by his own noblemen.",
        "answer_b": " Aslan stops the battle before anyone is killed.",
        "answer_c": " Peter is wounded when Miraz puts his full weight into his shield.",
        "answer_d": " King Miraz stumbles and falls flat on his face."
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Prince Caspian, what is the name of the Captain of the Mice, whom Aslan rewards with a new tail for the loyalty of his troops?",
        "correct_answer": " Reepicheep",
        "answer_a": " Peepicheek",
        "answer_b": " Cheekipeep",
        "answer_c": " Reepicheep",
        "answer_d": " Mickey"
    },
    {
        "question": "For what reason does King Miraz seek to kill Prince Caspian in the self-titled book?",
        "correct_answer": " Both of these",
        "answer_a": " Miraz has recently had a son who he wishes to appoint as his heir.",
        "answer_b": " Neither of these",
        "answer_c": " Caspian is the rightful king of Narnia.",
        "answer_d": " Both of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "Before leaving Narnia in the novel Prince Caspian, Aslan informs Peter and Edmund that neither of them will be returning to Narnia.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two creatures accompany Edmund as he delivers Peters challenge to King Miraz in the book Prince Caspian?",
        "correct_answer": " A giant and a centaur",
        "answer_a": " A bear and a squirrel",
        "answer_b": " A dwarf and a giant",
        "answer_c": " A giant and a centaur",
        "answer_d": " A mouse and a dwarf"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the novel Prince Caspian, which two people are responsible for Prince Caspians great interest in Old Narnia?",
        "correct_answer": " His old nurse and his tutor, Cornelius",
        "answer_a": " His old nurse and his tutor, Cornelius",
        "answer_b": " High King Peter and King Edmund",
        "answer_c": " The magician Cornelius and the lion, Aslan",
        "answer_d": " His aunt, the queen and the dwarf Rikabrik"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Tellmarines, featured in the novel Prince Caspian, are descendants of pirates that entered the land of Tellmar through a cave on an island.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Ravenclaws symbol in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Eagle",
        "answer_a": " Snake",
        "answer_b": " Bear",
        "answer_c": " Eagle",
        "answer_d": " Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which house is Susan Bones, one of the characters in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Hufflepuff",
        "answer_a": " Ravenclaw",
        "answer_b": " Hufflepuff",
        "answer_c": " Gryffindor",
        "answer_d": " Slytherin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is Remus Lupin related to Sirius Black?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who owned Scabbers before Ron Weasley?",
        "correct_answer": " Percy",
        "answer_a": " Percy",
        "answer_b": " Charlie",
        "answer_c": " Bill",
        "answer_d": " unknown by exact text"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ginny died in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter series, Rons uncle Billius saw a grim and died 25 hours later.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Harry Potter have a tattoo on his chest?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these Harry Potter characters is not a member of the D.A.?",
        "correct_answer": " Malfoy",
        "answer_a": " Luna",
        "answer_b": " Cho",
        "answer_c": " Malfoy",
        "answer_d": " Anthony"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Voldemorts followers called in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Death Eaters",
        "answer_a": " Death Munchers",
        "answer_b": " Death Eaters",
        "answer_c": " Death Masters",
        "answer_d": " Death Bugs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hermiones cats name is Crookshanks.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a name for Voldemort, the chief antagonist of the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Dark Master",
        "answer_a": " Dark Master",
        "answer_b": " Dark Lord",
        "answer_c": " You-Know-Who",
        "answer_d": " He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Luna Lovegoods father in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " Xenophilius",
        "answer_a": " Xewartqwe",
        "answer_b": " Piilotorpho",
        "answer_c": " Xenophilius",
        "answer_d": " Lenopillius"
    },
    {
        "question": "Professor Snape is the Potions Master in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was Grindelwald defeated by Dumbledore in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter marries Hermione.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Voldemort have a rat named Nagini?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Disney movie, The Beauty and the Beast, all of the residents of the Beasts castle were mystical creatures.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Emma Watson plays Hermione Granger in the Harry Potter film series.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What English actor portrays Harry Potters best friend, Ron Weasley?",
        "correct_answer": " Rupert Grint",
        "answer_a": " Rupert Grint",
        "answer_b": " Rupert Grant",
        "answer_c": " Hugh Mitchell",
        "answer_d": " Richard Harris"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Gryffindor House ghost does John Cleese play in the Harry Potter film series?",
        "correct_answer": " Nearly Headless Nick",
        "answer_a": " The Fat Friar",
        "answer_b": " Nearly Headless Nick",
        "answer_c": " Peeves The Poltergeist",
        "answer_d": " The Bloody Baron"
    },
    {
        "question": "What member of the Order of the Phoenix is portrayed by actor Robbie Coltrane?",
        "correct_answer": " Rubeus Hagrid",
        "answer_a": " Aberforth Dumbledore",
        "answer_b": " Rubeus Hagrid",
        "answer_c": " Bill Weasley",
        "answer_d": " Sirius Black"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name the first actor who played Professor Dumbledore in the Harry Potter film series.",
        "correct_answer": " Richard Harris",
        "answer_a": " Richard Martin",
        "answer_b": " Robbie Coltrane",
        "answer_c": " Richard Harris",
        "answer_d": " Richard Griffiths"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who portrays Draco Malfoy, one of the antagonists in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Tom Felton",
        "answer_a": " Tom Felton",
        "answer_b": " Alan Rickman",
        "answer_c": " Matthew Lewis",
        "answer_d": " David Bradley"
    },
    {
        "question": "What actor is not correctly paired with the character they played in the Harry Potter films?",
        "correct_answer": " Jason Isaacs - Lord Voldemort",
        "answer_a": " Emma Thompson - Sybill Trelawney",
        "answer_b": " Helena Bonham Carter - Bellatrix Lestrange",
        "answer_c": " Alan Rickman - Severus Snape",
        "answer_d": " Jason Isaacs - Lord Voldemort"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which potion in the Harry Potter series increases the luck of the drinker?",
        "correct_answer": " Felix Felicis",
        "answer_a": " Everlasting Elixirs",
        "answer_b": " Emerald Green Potion",
        "answer_c": " Confusing Concoction",
        "answer_d": " Felix Felicis"
    },
    {
        "question": "This potion from the Harry Potter books induces a deep dreamless sleep in the drinker.",
        "correct_answer": " Sleeping Draught",
        "answer_a": " Sleeping Draught",
        "answer_b": " Draught of Peace",
        "answer_c": " Forgetfulness Potion",
        "answer_d": " Calming Draught"
    },
    {
        "question": "What potion in the Harry Potter series helps stop bleeding and heal wounds?",
        "correct_answer": " Essence of Dittany",
        "answer_a": " Essence of Dittany",
        "answer_b": " Mandrake Restorative Draught",
        "answer_c": " Skele-Gro",
        "answer_d": " Amortentia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What potion relieves the symptoms of lycanthropy in the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Wolfsbane Potion",
        "answer_a": " Essence of Murtlap",
        "answer_b": " Wolfsbane Potion",
        "answer_c": " Beautification Potion",
        "answer_d": " Elixir of Life"
    },
    {
        "question": "This potion is described by J.K. Rowling as so powerful that three drops would have you spilling your innermost secrets for the entire class to hear.",
        "correct_answer": " Veritaserum",
        "answer_a": " Memory Potion",
        "answer_b": " Veritaserum",
        "answer_c": " Babbling Beverage",
        "answer_d": " Polyjuice Potion"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Harry Potter books, this potion causes the drinker to become infatuated or obsessed with the one who gave it to them.",
        "correct_answer": " Love Potion",
        "answer_a": " Wit-Sharpening Potion",
        "answer_b": " Elixir to Induce Euphoria",
        "answer_c": " Love Potion",
        "answer_d": " Pepperup Potion"
    },
    {
        "question": "This potion, mentioned in the Harry Potter books, allows the drinker to assume the appearance of another person.",
        "correct_answer": " Polyjuice Potion",
        "answer_a": " Befuddlement Draught",
        "answer_b": " Swelling Solution",
        "answer_c": " Skele-Gro",
        "answer_d": " Polyjuice Potion"
    },
    {
        "question": "What potion is used to help treat colds in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " Pepperup Potion",
        "answer_a": " Calming Draught",
        "answer_b": " Shrinking Solution",
        "answer_c": " Pepperup Potion",
        "answer_d": " Hiccoughing Solution"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which potion, introduced in Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone, lengthens the lifespan of the drinker as long as they keep drinking it?",
        "correct_answer": " Elixir of Life",
        "answer_a": " Strengthening Solution",
        "answer_b": " Mandrake Restorative Draft",
        "answer_c": " Draught of Living Death",
        "answer_d": " Elixir of Life"
    },
    {
        "question": "What potion from the Harry Potter books causes the drinker to become older?",
        "correct_answer": " Aging Potion",
        "answer_a": " Aging Potion",
        "answer_b": " Confusing Concoction",
        "answer_c": " Swelling Solution",
        "answer_d": " Befuddlement Draught"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Death Eater killed Fred Weasley in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " unknown by exact text",
        "answer_a": " Yaxley",
        "answer_b": " Bellatrix",
        "answer_c": " unknown by exact text",
        "answer_d": " Rookwood"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional character Severus Snape was a Death Eater when he died.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Death Eater bit Lupin?",
        "correct_answer": " Fenrir Greyback",
        "answer_a": " Fenrir Greyback",
        "answer_b": " Dolohov",
        "answer_c": " Rookwood",
        "answer_d": " Yaxley"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional character Augustus Rookwood worked in the Department of Mysteries.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the answer to the riddle the sphinx gives to Harry Potter in the maze for the third task of of the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "correct_answer": " spider",
        "answer_a": " spider",
        "answer_b": " spyglass",
        "answer_c": " spyer",
        "answer_d": " spurr"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the fourth champion of the fictional Triwizard Tournament?",
        "correct_answer": " Harry Potter",
        "answer_a": " Viktor Krum",
        "answer_b": " Fleur Delacour",
        "answer_c": " Harry Potter",
        "answer_d": " Cedric Diggory"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the chapter in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire in which Cedric Diggory dies?",
        "correct_answer": " Flesh, Blood, and Bone",
        "answer_a": " The Death Eaters",
        "answer_b": " Prior Incantatem",
        "answer_c": " The Third Task",
        "answer_d": " Flesh, Blood, and Bone"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Harry Potter fight a dementor in the maze in the third task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the dragon Viktor Krum has to fight for the first task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "correct_answer": " Chinese Fireball",
        "answer_a": " Swedish Shortsnout",
        "answer_b": " Chinese Fireball",
        "answer_c": " Welsh Green",
        "answer_d": " Hungarian Horntail"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Harry Potter do to be able to breathe underwater for the second task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
        "correct_answer": " eats gillyweed",
        "answer_a": " eats gillyweed",
        "answer_b": " uses breathing equipment",
        "answer_c": " uses bubblehead charm",
        "answer_d": " transforms into a shark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is Harry Potter when he finds out what the second task of the Triwizard Tournament is about?",
        "correct_answer": " prefects bathroom",
        "answer_a": " prefects bathroom",
        "answer_b": " girls bathroom",
        "answer_c": " teachers bathroom",
        "answer_d": " boys bathroom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter wins 10,000 galleons for winning the Triwizard Tournament.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year was the novel Anne of Green Gables published?",
        "correct_answer": " 1908",
        "answer_a": " 1919",
        "answer_b": " 1908",
        "answer_c": " 1925",
        "answer_d": " 1955"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the location of the orphanage from which Anne was adopted in the book Anne of Green Gables?",
        "correct_answer": " Nova Scotia",
        "answer_a": " New Brunswick",
        "answer_b": " Maine",
        "answer_c": " Nova Scotia",
        "answer_d": " Newfoundland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the relationship between Matthew and Marilla, the couple who adopted Anne in Lucy Montgomerys book?",
        "correct_answer": " Brother and Sister",
        "answer_a": " Father and Daughter",
        "answer_b": " Husband and Wife",
        "answer_c": " Brother and Sister",
        "answer_d": " They were cousins"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many books are there in the L. M. Montgomery Anne series?",
        "correct_answer": " 8",
        "answer_a": " 5",
        "answer_b": " 8",
        "answer_c": " 3",
        "answer_d": " 10"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Anne of Green Gables Anne gets herself into many predicaments.  Which of the following is NOT one of them?",
        "correct_answer": " She mistook a bottle of currant wine for the raspberry cordial she was supposed to serve for tea and got drunk.",
        "answer_a": " She mistook a bottle of currant wine for the raspberry cordial she was supposed to serve for tea and got drunk.",
        "answer_b": " She forgot to replace the cheesecloth cover on the pudding sauce and a mouse drowned in it.",
        "answer_c": " She bought hair dye from a peddler and instead of the desired black, it turned her hair green.",
        "answer_d": " She broke her slate over a schoolmates head when he teasingly called her carrots."
    },
    {
        "question": "In what Canadian province do Marilla and Matthew Cuthbert live in the book Anne of Green Gables?",
        "correct_answer": " Prince Edward Island",
        "answer_a": " None of these",
        "answer_b": " Prince Edward Island",
        "answer_c": " New Brunswick",
        "answer_d": " Nova Scotia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the fictional town in which the story of Anne of Green Gables unfolds?",
        "correct_answer": " Avonlea",
        "answer_a": " Carmody",
        "answer_b": " Cavendish",
        "answer_c": " Avonlea",
        "answer_d": " White Sands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is Annes surname in the book Anne of Green Gables?",
        "correct_answer": " Shirley",
        "answer_a": " Pye",
        "answer_b": " Blythe",
        "answer_c": " Shirley",
        "answer_d": " Cuthbert"
    },
    {
        "question": "Diana Barry is Annes best friend in the book Anne of Green Gables. How did Anne describe their friendship?",
        "correct_answer": " Bosom friends",
        "answer_a": " Two peas in a pod",
        "answer_b": " Bosom friends",
        "answer_c": " Truer than blue",
        "answer_d": " Friends til the end"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was Anne of Green Gables - The Musical performed for the first time?",
        "correct_answer": " 1964",
        "answer_a": " 1960",
        "answer_b": " 1964",
        "answer_c": " 1970",
        "answer_d": " 1972"
    },
    {
        "question": "Early in the story of Anne of Green Gables, Marilla proudly presents Anne with three new dresses which she has made to replace the shabby, orphanage issued clothes but is very annoyed when it becomes obvious that Anne doesnt like them. Why doesnt Anne like them?",
        "correct_answer": " They dont have puffed sleeves.",
        "answer_a": " They dont have flounces.",
        "answer_b": " They dont have petticoats.",
        "answer_c": " They dont have puffed sleeves.",
        "answer_d": " They dont have any lace trimming."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the theater in which Anne of Green Gables - The Musical plays every summer?",
        "correct_answer": " The Confederation Center of the Arts",
        "answer_a": " The Green Gables Theater of the Arts",
        "answer_b": " The Cradle of Confederation Theater",
        "answer_c": " The Centennial Theater of the Arts",
        "answer_d": " The Confederation Center of the Arts"
    },
    {
        "question": "This Emmy Award-winning actress played Marilla in the 1985 television production of Anne of Green Gables, written and directed by Kevin Sullivan.",
        "correct_answer": " Colleen Dewhurst",
        "answer_a": " Colleen Dewhurst",
        "answer_b": " Ellen Burstyn",
        "answer_c": " Patricia Hamilton",
        "answer_d": " Rosemary Radcliff"
    },
    {
        "question": "What adjective best describes the character of Mrs. Rachel Lynde from the book Anne of Green Gables?",
        "correct_answer": " All of these",
        "answer_a": " All of these",
        "answer_b": " Bossy",
        "answer_c": " Prying",
        "answer_d": " Opinionated"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the end of the novel Anne of Green Gables, Matthew Cuthbert dies from complications related to pneumonia.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sam had $3.00, Bob had $9.50, Joe had $5.25, and Jim had $7.25. How much is all of their money together worth?",
        "correct_answer": " $25.00",
        "answer_a": " $2.50",
        "answer_b": " $250.00",
        "answer_c": " $25.00",
        "answer_d": " $25.50"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these numbers does not fit in the sequence: 2 4 6 7 9 12 11?",
        "correct_answer": " 12",
        "answer_a": " 11",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 12",
        "answer_d": " 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you get when you divide 123 by 10?",
        "correct_answer": " 12.3",
        "answer_a": " 32.1",
        "answer_b": " 3.21",
        "answer_c": " 1.23",
        "answer_d": " 12.3"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are three digits in this number. The first digit (of the hundreds) is 8. Divide it by two, that is your second digit, divide the result again by two, that is your third digit. What is the number?",
        "correct_answer": " 842",
        "answer_a": " 284",
        "answer_b": " 824",
        "answer_c": " 428",
        "answer_d": " 842"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do all of these numbers fit the sequence: 1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 9?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much is 765 divided by 10?",
        "correct_answer": " 76.5",
        "answer_a": " 74.5",
        "answer_b": " 76.5",
        "answer_c": " 76",
        "answer_d": " 75"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following numbers doesnt belong to the others: 3, 9, 15, 20?",
        "correct_answer": " 20",
        "answer_a": " 3",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 15",
        "answer_d": " 20"
    },
    {
        "question": "A person owned 8 dogs and as many cats. What is the total amount of pets owned by that somebody?",
        "correct_answer": " 16",
        "answer_a": " 16",
        "answer_b": " 32",
        "answer_c": " 8",
        "answer_d": " 4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first Horcrux found in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " The locket",
        "answer_a": " Hufflepuffs cup",
        "answer_b": " The locket",
        "answer_c": " None of these",
        "answer_d": " Nagini"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did Harry Potter destroy Tom Riddles diary in the second book because he knew it was a Horcrux?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Ron and Hermione use to destroy Hufflepuffs cup?",
        "correct_answer": " Basilisk Fangs",
        "answer_a": " Gryffindors sword",
        "answer_b": " Their Wands",
        "answer_c": " Nothing, Harry destroyed it.",
        "answer_d": " Basilisk Fangs"
    },
    {
        "question": "One of the Horcruxes in the Harry Potter books is Ravenclaws cup.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Horcruxes did Tom Riddle make?",
        "correct_answer": " 7",
        "answer_a": " 10",
        "answer_b": " 7",
        "answer_c": " 2",
        "answer_d": " 5"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the Harry Potter series of books, any object can be a Horcrux.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "If one of Voldemorts Horcruxes is destroyed, will he know?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nagini, one of Voldemorts Horcruxes, is a snake.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "How old was Charlotte, the protagonist of The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, when she took the trip from England to her home on Rhode Island?",
        "correct_answer": " 13",
        "answer_a": " 13",
        "answer_b": " 55",
        "answer_c": " 22",
        "answer_d": " 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the name of the ship that Charlotte boarded in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle?",
        "correct_answer": " The Seahawk",
        "answer_a": " The Seahawk",
        "answer_b": " The Seacraft",
        "answer_c": " The Doyle Express",
        "answer_d": " The Charlotte Doyle"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, the crew wanted to get revenge on the Captain.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Charlotte was the only female on the ship in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, the men from the crew plan to kill Charlotte because she supported the Captain.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Zachariah, a character from the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, is brutally beaten to death by the Captain and Mr. Hollybrass.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does the Captain blame for the murder of Mr. Hollybrass in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle?",
        "correct_answer": " Charlotte",
        "answer_a": " Charlotte",
        "answer_b": " The ships ghost",
        "answer_c": " Himself",
        "answer_d": " Zachariah"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, what is the penalty for murder of a ships First Mate?",
        "correct_answer": " hanging",
        "answer_a": " hanging",
        "answer_b": " a week in the brig",
        "answer_c": " getting your hands cut off",
        "answer_d": " getting locked in a room with the ships ghost"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Captain in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle dies.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Sea Witch want from the Little Mermaid in exchange for the magic potion in Andersens fairy tale The Little Mermaid?",
        "correct_answer": " Her tongue/voice",
        "answer_a": " Her soul",
        "answer_b": " Her heart",
        "answer_c": " Her tongue/voice",
        "answer_d": " Her necklace"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the meaning of a falling star according to the late grandmother in Andersens The Little Match Girl?",
        "correct_answer": " Someone is dying",
        "answer_a": " Someone is dying",
        "answer_b": " God is crying",
        "answer_c": " Someone is born",
        "answer_d": " An angel is coming to earth from Heaven"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens to the pea after the prince marries the princess in the fairy tale The Princess and the Pea?",
        "correct_answer": " They put it in the Royal Museum",
        "answer_a": " They put it in the Royal Museum",
        "answer_b": " They split it and eat it",
        "answer_c": " An anger takes it to Heaven",
        "answer_d": " A dove eats it"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Elisa forbidden to do until she finishes knitting the eleven nettle shirts in Hans Christian Andersens fairy tale The Wild Swans?",
        "correct_answer": " Speak",
        "answer_a": " Smile",
        "answer_b": " Cut her hair",
        "answer_c": " Go out in the sunlight",
        "answer_d": " Speak"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the word that Kai has to spell using pieces of ice in order to regain his freedom in Andersens fairy tale The Snow Queen?",
        "correct_answer": " Eternity",
        "answer_a": " Forgiveness",
        "answer_b": " Eternity",
        "answer_c": " Love",
        "answer_d": " Purity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What new name is Thumbelina given at the end of the fairy tale Thumbelina?",
        "correct_answer": " Maya",
        "answer_a": " Bella",
        "answer_b": " Rosalind",
        "answer_c": " Maya",
        "answer_d": " Lily"
    },
    {
        "question": "What animals mock the little duck in Hans Christian Andersens fairy tale The Ugly Duckling?",
        "correct_answer": " Cat and hen",
        "answer_a": " Cat and dog",
        "answer_b": " Cat and hen",
        "answer_c": " Hen and dog",
        "answer_d": " Geese"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of people are unable to see the clothes of the emperor according to the frauds in the fairy tale The Emperors New Clothes?",
        "correct_answer": " Stupid people",
        "answer_a": " Liars",
        "answer_b": " Stupid people",
        "answer_c": " Criminals",
        "answer_d": " All of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to The Steadfast Tin Soldier, what do the tin soldier and the paper ballerina have in common that makes the soldier fall in love?",
        "correct_answer": " They are both standing on one leg",
        "answer_a": " They are dressed in white",
        "answer_b": " They are both standing on one leg",
        "answer_c": " They love listening to the gramophone",
        "answer_d": " They are both very sad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does Death decide to spare the Chinese Emperors life in the fairy tale The Nightingale by Hans Christian Andersen?",
        "correct_answer": " He is moved by the song of the bird",
        "answer_a": " God forces him to go away",
        "answer_b": " He is moved by the song of the bird",
        "answer_c": " He takes the Emperors nightingale in exchange for his life",
        "answer_d": " He gets scared from a Chinese mask"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people died in the fictional Battle of Hogwarts?",
        "correct_answer": " 54",
        "answer_a": " 54",
        "answer_b": " 50",
        "answer_c": " 52",
        "answer_d": " 53"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people are in the fictional student organisation known as Dumbledores Army?",
        "correct_answer": " 28",
        "answer_a": " 25",
        "answer_b": " 26",
        "answer_c": " 29",
        "answer_d": " 28"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many siblings does Ron Weasley have?",
        "correct_answer": " 6",
        "answer_a": " 3",
        "answer_b": " 5",
        "answer_c": " 4",
        "answer_d": " 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people were selected for the Triwizard Tournament in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire?",
        "correct_answer": " 4",
        "answer_a": " 5",
        "answer_b": " 1",
        "answer_c": " 4",
        "answer_d": " 3"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many O.W.L.s did Hermione Granger get in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " 10",
        "answer_a": " 15",
        "answer_b": " 9",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 8"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many dementors attacked Harry and Hermione in the end of Book 3 of the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " 50",
        "answer_a": " 55",
        "answer_b": " 45",
        "answer_c": " 40",
        "answer_d": " 50"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many floors are in the fictional Hogwarts school?(excluding the dungeons)",
        "correct_answer": " 7",
        "answer_a": " 9",
        "answer_b": " 8",
        "answer_c": " 6",
        "answer_d": " 7"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what day did Harry Potter discover the Mirror of Erised?",
        "correct_answer": " December 25th",
        "answer_a": " December 25th",
        "answer_b": " November 25th",
        "answer_c": " October 25th",
        "answer_d": " January 25th"
    },
    {
        "question": "On what floor of the fictional Hogwarts school do you find the Room of Requirement?",
        "correct_answer": " 7th",
        "answer_a": " 5th",
        "answer_b": " 7th",
        "answer_c": " 6th",
        "answer_d": " 3rd"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many people died in the book Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone?",
        "correct_answer": " 3",
        "answer_a": " 2",
        "answer_b": " 3",
        "answer_c": " 4",
        "answer_d": " 1"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Harrys first line in the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " What the?",
        "answer_a": " Whats this doing here?",
        "answer_b": " Ouch!",
        "answer_c": " Hush up Hedwig",
        "answer_d": " What the?"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fictional character Rita Skeeter wrote a book titled Albus Dumbledore, His Life and Lies.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Was Albus Dumbledores sister named Areida?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Hermione Granger fly with when leaving Privet Drive?",
        "correct_answer": " Kingsley Shacklebolt",
        "answer_a": " Fred Weasley",
        "answer_b": " Arthur Weasley",
        "answer_c": " Kingsley Shacklebolt",
        "answer_d": " Bill Weasley"
    },
    {
        "question": "What spell does Hermione not approve of according to the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " Muffliato",
        "answer_a": " Suctesemptra",
        "answer_b": " Muffliato",
        "answer_c": " Demuestio",
        "answer_d": " Fiendfyre"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Ron leaves the group when they are in the forest of Dean.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What character first discovered that the name Voldemort was cursed?",
        "correct_answer": " Ron",
        "answer_a": " Ron",
        "answer_b": " Harry",
        "answer_c": " Hermione",
        "answer_d": " Ginny"
    },
    {
        "question": "It is mentioned in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows that Bill had a real knack for guessing the passwords for the radio.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Harry first use the Imperius curse on in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " A goblin",
        "answer_a": " Dragomir",
        "answer_b": " He doesnt use unforgivable curses.",
        "answer_c": " A goblin",
        "answer_d": " Travers"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the Harry Potter books, Fleur Delacours middle name is Clemence.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the spell that multiplies objects in the Harry Potter books?",
        "correct_answer": " Gemino",
        "answer_a": " Gemino",
        "answer_b": " Duplique",
        "answer_c": " Multiplico",
        "answer_d": " Magrante"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the chapter of Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows, titled The Princes Tale, Lily states that these two boys idea of humor is, just evil.",
        "correct_answer": " Mulciber and Avery",
        "answer_a": " Mulciber and Avery",
        "answer_b": " Macnair and Lucius",
        "answer_c": " James and Sirius",
        "answer_d": " Lucius and Lestrange"
    },
    {
        "question": "What characters screams at the end of Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows on learning of Harrys apparent death.",
        "correct_answer": " McGonagall",
        "answer_a": " Hermione",
        "answer_b": " McGonagall",
        "answer_c": " Ginny",
        "answer_d": " Ron"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Voldemort tell Neville that he has spirit and bravery in the last book of the Harry Potter series?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sleeping Beauty was the last fairy tale produced by Walt Disney.  When was it released?",
        "correct_answer": " January 29, 1959",
        "answer_a": " May 25, 1944",
        "answer_b": " January 29, 1959",
        "answer_c": " August 1, 1966",
        "answer_d": " February 14, 1951"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sleeping Beautys musical score and songs were inspired by Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovskys Sleeping Beauty ballet.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, Princess Aurora is born to King Stefan and Queen Leah and they name her Aurora after what Roman goddess?",
        "correct_answer": " The goddess of the dawn",
        "answer_a": " The goddess of the dawn",
        "answer_b": " The goddess of the moon",
        "answer_c": " The goddess of the forests",
        "answer_d": " The goddess of the clouds"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the popular Disney animated film Maleficent curses baby Aurora: she will die when she pricks her finger on a spinning wheels spindle.  Why does Maleficent arrive and curse the child?",
        "correct_answer": " She was not invited to the christening.",
        "answer_a": " She was in line to inherit the kingdom before Aurora was born.",
        "answer_b": " She is in love with the king.",
        "answer_c": " She hates the queen, her sister.",
        "answer_d": " She was not invited to the christening."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the gift of the third fairy in the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty?",
        "correct_answer": " She weakens the curse so Aurora will only fall into a deep sleep.",
        "answer_a": " She makes Aurora able to live for 500 years.",
        "answer_b": " She weakens the curse so Aurora will only fall into a deep sleep.",
        "answer_c": " She curses Maleficent with death.",
        "answer_d": " She makes a valiant prince fall in love with Aurora."
    },
    {
        "question": "The three fairies in the animated film Sleeping Beauty decide to conceal Aurora in a cabin in the woods until her 16th birthday passes, but before the fairies take Aurora to the woods, what does the King do to stop the curse?",
        "correct_answer": " commands all spinning wheels be destroyed",
        "answer_a": " locks Aurora in a tower",
        "answer_b": " tries to have another witch remove the curse",
        "answer_c": " commands all spinning wheels be destroyed",
        "answer_d": " kills Maleficent"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do the fairies rename Aurora in the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty?",
        "correct_answer": " Briar Rose",
        "answer_a": " Dahlia",
        "answer_b": " Topaz",
        "answer_c": " Briar Rose",
        "answer_d": " Jasmine"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the animated movie Sleeping Beauty, just prior to Auroras 16th birthday, Maleficent is furious that she and her evil henchmen still cannot find Aurora. What does Maleficent do?",
        "correct_answer": " She sends out her raven Diablo to find Aurora.",
        "answer_a": " She consults her crystal ball for Aurora.",
        "answer_b": " She sends out her raven Diablo to find Aurora.",
        "answer_c": " She disguises herself as a peasant and searches for Aurora.",
        "answer_d": " She puts the prince under a spell and sends him to search for Aurora."
    },
    {
        "question": "In the movie Sleeping Beauty, on Auroras 16th birthday, the fairies decide to make two presents, but their attempts fail and they use their wands, thus giving away their location. What two items were the fairies making for Aurora?",
        "correct_answer": " A cake and a gown",
        "answer_a": " A gown and a cape",
        "answer_b": " A cake and a gown",
        "answer_c": " A cake and a quilt",
        "answer_d": " A pie and a gown"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, when Aurora returns to the cabin, the fairies tell her who she really is and take her to the castle to see her parents.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the movie Sleeping Beauty, back at home in the castle, Aurora finds a spinning wheel in the castles tower, pricks her finger on the spindle and falls into a deep sleep. Who finds Aurora?",
        "correct_answer": " The fairies",
        "answer_a": " The queen",
        "answer_b": " The king",
        "answer_c": " The fairies",
        "answer_d": " The prince"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, once Aurora falls into her deep sleep, the fairies freeze time until the spell is broken.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Disney film Sleeping Beauty, the fairies find out that Prince Phillip is the man Aurora loves and the only one who can break the spell, but Maleficents henchmen capture him and take him to Maleficents castle. What is the castle called?",
        "correct_answer": " The Forbidden Mountain",
        "answer_a": " The Lair",
        "answer_b": " The Den of Thorns",
        "answer_c": " The Forbidden Mountain",
        "answer_d": " The Dark Palace"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the animated movie Sleeping Beauty, the fairies enter Maleficents castle and free the prince and give him these two magical objects.",
        "correct_answer": " A sword and a shield",
        "answer_a": " A robe and sword",
        "answer_b": " A watch and a book",
        "answer_c": " A sword and a shield",
        "answer_d": " A rose and a robe"
    },
    {
        "question": "After Maleficent dies in the film Sleeping Beauty, Prince Phillip rushes to Aurora and removes the curse with a kiss. The two enter the palaces ballroom and see Auroras parents. Is this the first time Aurora has seen her parents since she was an infant?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the animated film Sleeping Beauty, Aurora and Prince Phillip dance a waltz and do not notice the fairies magically changing the color of Auroras ball gown.  As the book closes, Auroras gown turns this color and remains this color.",
        "correct_answer": " Pink",
        "answer_a": " Pink",
        "answer_b": " Blue",
        "answer_c": " Purple",
        "answer_d": " Green"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sleeping Beauty was re-released theatrically in 1970, 1971, 1986, 1993, 1995, and 2008. How much did it gross in theatres in the period 1959-2009, when adjusted for ticket price inflation?",
        "correct_answer": " $478.22 million",
        "answer_a": " $102.49 million",
        "answer_b": " $478.22 million",
        "answer_c": " $668.39 million",
        "answer_d": " $309.2 million"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did actress Emma Watson, who plays Hermione in the Harry Potter series, keep her role in the sixth movie, Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009, after initially deciding to quit?",
        "correct_answer": " She couldnt bear to see anyone else play Hermione.",
        "answer_a": " She joked that she stayed because she was in love with Rupert Grint.",
        "answer_b": " Her parents talked her into staying.",
        "answer_c": " She did it for the fans.",
        "answer_d": " She couldnt bear to see anyone else play Hermione."
    },
    {
        "question": "How did actor Jim Broadbent describe his character, Horace Slughorn, from the sixth Harry Potter movie, Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009?",
        "correct_answer": " Comic character",
        "answer_a": " Comic character",
        "answer_b": " Unique character",
        "answer_c": " Tragic character",
        "answer_d": " Ambiguous character"
    },
    {
        "question": "This actress reportedly accepted the role of Narcissa Malfoy for the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, but her agent stated that the rumors were not true.",
        "correct_answer": " Naomi Watts",
        "answer_a": " Kate Winslet",
        "answer_b": " Meg Ryan",
        "answer_c": " Naomi Watts",
        "answer_d": " Melanie Griffith"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who turns out to be the Half-Blood Prince in the sixth Harry Potter movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Severus Snape",
        "answer_a": " Draco Malfoy",
        "answer_b": " Albus Dumbledore",
        "answer_c": " Severus Snape",
        "answer_d": " Sirius Black"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nickname of Sirius Black, whose younger brother Regulus Black appears in a photograph owned by Horace Slughorn in the movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009?",
        "correct_answer": " Padfoot",
        "answer_a": " Bagger",
        "answer_b": " Padfoot",
        "answer_c": " Mole",
        "answer_d": " Dazzler"
    },
    {
        "question": "With whom does Harry Potter form a relationship in the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Ginny Weasley",
        "answer_a": " Fleur Delacour",
        "answer_b": " Lavender Brown",
        "answer_c": " All of these",
        "answer_d": " Ginny Weasley"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the differences between the original plot of the book and the script of 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Both the battle in the castle and Dumbledores funeral were not in the script.",
        "answer_a": " Dumbledores funeral was not in the script.",
        "answer_b": " Both the battle in the castle and Dumbledores funeral were not in the script.",
        "answer_c": " The climactic battle in the castle was not in the script.",
        "answer_d": " No changes were made."
    },
    {
        "question": "What popular personality did actor Daniel Radcliffe portray in his debut movie?",
        "correct_answer": " David Copperfield",
        "answer_a": " David Copperfield",
        "answer_b": " Peter Pan",
        "answer_c": " Adolf Hitler",
        "answer_d": " Harry Potter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of character did actor Rupert Grint from the 2009 Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince depict in a play based on the story of Noahs Ark when he was little?",
        "correct_answer": " A fish",
        "answer_a": " One of Noahs sons",
        "answer_b": " A lion",
        "answer_c": " Noah",
        "answer_d": " A fish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these cast members of the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince was born in Paris, France?",
        "correct_answer": " Emma Watson",
        "answer_a": " Helena Bonham Carter",
        "answer_b": " Jessie Cave",
        "answer_c": " Bonnie Wright",
        "answer_d": " Emma Watson"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of bird is the character from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Happy Prince?",
        "correct_answer": " Swallow",
        "answer_a": " Nightingale",
        "answer_b": " Sparrow",
        "answer_c": " Hummingbird",
        "answer_d": " Swallow"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does the nightingale from Oscar Wildes story The Nightingale and the Rose find a red rose for the poor student?",
        "correct_answer": " It paints a white rose with its blood",
        "answer_a": " It steals one",
        "answer_b": " It paints a white rose with its blood",
        "answer_c": " It travels trough many countries and dies from exhaustion",
        "answer_d": " It prays to God and He sends one"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happens to the beautiful garden of the giant when he builds a wall to keep children off in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Selfish Giant?",
        "correct_answer": " Eternal winter sets in the garden",
        "answer_a": " There is no more sunshine in the garden, only darkness",
        "answer_b": " The small pond dries up and the fish dies",
        "answer_c": " All the flowers wither and the birds die",
        "answer_d": " Eternal winter sets in the garden"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does Hans from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Devoted Friend do for a living?",
        "correct_answer": " Hes a gardener",
        "answer_a": " He is a musician",
        "answer_b": " He is a miller",
        "answer_c": " Hes a gardener",
        "answer_d": " Hes a doctor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does the rocket from Oscar Wildes story The Remarkable Rocket fail to ignite?",
        "correct_answer": " It gets wet",
        "answer_a": " It is too lofty",
        "answer_b": " It dies",
        "answer_c": " It is faulty",
        "answer_d": " It gets wet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why does the shepherd from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Young King refuse to wear the royal raiment?",
        "correct_answer": " He has nightmares of where it came from",
        "answer_a": " He doesnt want to be a king",
        "answer_b": " He has nightmares of where it came from",
        "answer_c": " All of these",
        "answer_d": " He finds it ugly"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the last line of the Infanta from Oscar Wildes story The Birthday of the Infanta?",
        "correct_answer": " For the future, let those who come to play with me have no hearts.",
        "answer_a": " Its a shame Ive forgotten who I was, so let the people decide my fate.",
        "answer_b": " For the future, let those who come to play with me have no hearts.",
        "answer_c": " Little people will never know what its like being a princess.",
        "answer_d": " Justice shall reign one day when I sit on the throne."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the Soul want from the fisherman in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Fisherman and his Soul?",
        "correct_answer": " His heart",
        "answer_a": " His only child",
        "answer_b": " His hope",
        "answer_c": " His most valuable possession",
        "answer_d": " His heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the mother of the Star-Child from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Star-Child?",
        "correct_answer": " A beggar",
        "answer_a": " A beggar",
        "answer_b": " An angel",
        "answer_c": " A witch",
        "answer_d": " A star"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the beautiful Star-Child transformed into in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Star-Child?",
        "correct_answer": " A cross between a snake and a toad",
        "answer_a": " A cross between a snake and a toad",
        "answer_b": " A flower",
        "answer_c": " Vapor",
        "answer_d": " A black dove"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter, Voldemort, and Dumbledore have connected wands.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these fictional characters is the leader of the Death Eaters?",
        "correct_answer": " Voldemort",
        "answer_a": " Voldemort",
        "answer_b": " Rookwood",
        "answer_c": " Bellatrix",
        "answer_d": " Igor Karkaroff"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first name of the animated 1980s hero Blackstar?",
        "correct_answer": " John",
        "answer_a": " Michael",
        "answer_b": " John",
        "answer_c": " Robert",
        "answer_d": " James"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did Blackstar from the animated series of the same name get stranded in the alien world?",
        "correct_answer": " After falling in a black hole",
        "answer_a": " After an impact with an asteroid",
        "answer_b": " Because of his co-pilots incompetence",
        "answer_c": " After a time rift",
        "answer_d": " After falling in a black hole"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what year were the Blackstar animated series first broadcast on American television?",
        "correct_answer": " 1981",
        "answer_a": " 1980",
        "answer_b": " 1981",
        "answer_c": " 1983",
        "answer_d": " 1979"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Blackstar animates series, which of these was not a name of the little people known as the Trobbits?",
        "correct_answer": " Dargo",
        "answer_a": " Burble",
        "answer_b": " Carpo",
        "answer_c": " Dargo",
        "answer_d": " Balkar"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many episodes of the animated series Blackstar ran on American television?",
        "correct_answer": " 13",
        "answer_a": " 16",
        "answer_b": " 13",
        "answer_c": " 20",
        "answer_d": " 10"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Wind in the Willows was published in 1908 without much notice. What famous author and playwright, best known for Winnie the Pooh, adapted part of the book for the stage in 1929, thus making the book famous?",
        "correct_answer": " A. A. Milne",
        "answer_a": " William Horwood",
        "answer_b": " E. H. Shepard",
        "answer_c": " Kenneth Grahame",
        "answer_d": " A. A. Milne"
    },
    {
        "question": "At the beginning of the book The Wind in the Willows, what is Mole doing when he gets angry and goes above ground to the river?",
        "correct_answer": " spring cleaning",
        "answer_a": " trying to sleep",
        "answer_b": " listening to Mr. Toad",
        "answer_c": " spring cleaning",
        "answer_d": " looking for food"
    },
    {
        "question": "What character from The Wind in the Willows becomes easily obsessed with items, only to forget about them soon after acquiring them?",
        "correct_answer": " Mr. Toad",
        "answer_a": " Mole",
        "answer_b": " Mr. Toad",
        "answer_c": " Weasel",
        "answer_d": " Pan"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Wind in the Willows was first published in 1908. What Scottish-born writer and author of the story The Reluctant Dragon wrote this book?",
        "correct_answer": " Kenneth Grahame",
        "answer_a": " E. H. Shepard",
        "answer_b": " A. A. Milne",
        "answer_c": " Kenneth Grahame",
        "answer_d": " James Blish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What character from The Wind in the Willows gets lost in Wild Wood while looking for Badgers house?",
        "correct_answer": " Mole",
        "answer_a": " Otter",
        "answer_b": " Mr. Toad",
        "answer_c": " Mole",
        "answer_d": " Weasel"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the novel The Wind in the Willows, Toad has crashed 6 cars, been put in the hospital for injuries 3 times, and has spent a great deal of money on fines. Toads friends decide to do this to save Toad since he has no sense when it comes to his obsessions.",
        "correct_answer": " Put him under house arrest",
        "answer_a": " Put him under house arrest",
        "answer_b": " Have him thrown in jail",
        "answer_c": " Burn his cars",
        "answer_d": " Make him live underground with Mole"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the novel The Wind in the Willows, while Mr. Toad is in jail, this person becomes fond of him and helps him escape.",
        "correct_answer": " The jailers daughter",
        "answer_a": " Toads cellmate",
        "answer_b": " The jailer",
        "answer_c": " Toads attorney",
        "answer_d": " The jailers daughter"
    },
    {
        "question": "In order to escape, Toad from The Wind in the Willows is dressed in disguise. What is he disguised as?",
        "correct_answer": " A washerwoman",
        "answer_a": " A police officer",
        "answer_b": " An attractive female",
        "answer_c": " The jailer",
        "answer_d": " A washerwoman"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book The Wind in the Willows, shortly after his escape and still in disguise, Mr. Toad meets a bargewoman and tricks her into giving him a job. The bargewoman discovers Toads trick and throws him overboard. He steals her horse and sells it to a Gypsy for what?",
        "correct_answer": " Money and stew",
        "answer_a": " Money and stew",
        "answer_b": " A ride back to Toad Hall",
        "answer_c": " Another disguise",
        "answer_d": " A place to spend the night"
    },
    {
        "question": "In The Wind in the Willows, Mr. Toad tries to hitchhike back to the River Bank community. What is the significance of the car and driver that give Toad a ride?",
        "correct_answer": " It is the same car that Toad stole earlier",
        "answer_a": " It is Toads car, and Badger is the driver",
        "answer_b": " It is Rats car, and Badger is the driver",
        "answer_c": " It is the same car that Toad stole earlier",
        "answer_d": " It is an undercover police car"
    },
    {
        "question": "After his jail escape, The Wind in the Willows character, Toad, learns from Ratty that Toad Hall has been taken over by these Wild Wood animals.",
        "correct_answer": " the weasels, stoats and ferrets",
        "answer_a": " the weasels, stoats and ferrets",
        "answer_b": " the rabbits and otters",
        "answer_c": " the birds",
        "answer_d": " the squirrels and chipmunks"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1949 Disney released their animated versions of The Wind in the Willows and this short story.",
        "correct_answer": " The Legend of Sleepy Hollow",
        "answer_a": " Chicken Little",
        "answer_b": " Rip Van Winkle",
        "answer_c": " The Legend of Sleepy Hollow",
        "answer_d": " Mickey and the Beanstalk"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1967 this British rock band released their first album. It was titled after Chapter 7 of The Wind in the Willows: The Piper at the Gates of Dawn.",
        "correct_answer": " Pink Floyd",
        "answer_a": " The Doors",
        "answer_b": " Jethro Tull",
        "answer_c": " The Beatles",
        "answer_d": " Pink Floyd"
    },
    {
        "question": "Based on Mr. Toads car driving in The Wind in the Willows, Mr. Toads Wild Ride was established in 1955. What is it?",
        "correct_answer": " a ride at Disneyland",
        "answer_a": " a ride at Disneyland",
        "answer_b": " a brand of tennis shoes",
        "answer_c": " a Wyoming state police manual",
        "answer_d": " a board game"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does Peter live in the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
        "correct_answer": " Mollusk Island",
        "answer_a": " Fairy Hollow",
        "answer_b": " London",
        "answer_c": " Never Land",
        "answer_d": " Mollusk Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Peter and the Shadow Thieves, what is the name of Fighting Prawns oldest daughter?",
        "correct_answer": " Shining Pearl",
        "answer_a": " Raven",
        "answer_b": " Dana",
        "answer_c": " Brilliant Ruby",
        "answer_d": " Shining Pearl"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does Peter, the main character in Peter and the Shadow Thieves, wear shoes?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the mermaid that flirts with Peter in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
        "correct_answer": " Teacher",
        "answer_a": " Singer",
        "answer_b": " Beauty",
        "answer_c": " Teacher",
        "answer_d": " Swimmer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who does Peter have to warn about Ombra in the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
        "correct_answer": " Molly",
        "answer_a": " Louise",
        "answer_b": " Tina",
        "answer_c": " Molly",
        "answer_d": " Julie"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves, Slank is one of the Aster guards.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does Peter get to London in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
        "correct_answer": " He goes by boat.",
        "answer_a": " He takes a taxi.",
        "answer_b": " He goes by boat.",
        "answer_c": " He flies.",
        "answer_d": " He swims."
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves, the starstuff was in what tower?",
        "correct_answer": " White Tower",
        "answer_a": " Bloody Tower",
        "answer_b": " White Tower",
        "answer_c": " Prison Tower",
        "answer_d": " Golden Tower"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves, James and Thomas are the two fastest Lost boys.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fairy is Peters guardian in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
        "correct_answer": " Tinker Bell",
        "answer_a": " Rosy Tone",
        "answer_b": " Hornblower",
        "answer_c": " Tinker Bell",
        "answer_d": " Violet Vinger"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, when Harry is visiting Weasleys Wizard Wheezes, what is the last product mentioned before he followed Draco Malfoy into Knockturn Alley?",
        "correct_answer": " Pygmy Puff",
        "answer_a": " Decoy Detonator",
        "answer_b": " Pygmy Puff",
        "answer_c": " Fever Fudge",
        "answer_d": " Nose Bleed Nougat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of tree does Harry Potter sit under after Dumbledores funeral?",
        "correct_answer": " Beech",
        "answer_a": " Beech",
        "answer_b": " Whomping Willow",
        "answer_c": " Spruce",
        "answer_d": " Oak"
    },
    {
        "question": "The first time Harry Potter encounters a little girl outside the room of requirement, she drops a bottle of what?",
        "correct_answer": " Toadspawn",
        "answer_a": " Water",
        "answer_b": " Dittany",
        "answer_c": " Draught of Living Death",
        "answer_d": " Toadspawn"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Bellatrix Lestranges wand made of?",
        "correct_answer": " Walnut",
        "answer_a": " Pine",
        "answer_b": " Walnut",
        "answer_c": " Oak",
        "answer_d": " Chestnut"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Zoeys last name on the TV show Zoey 101?",
        "correct_answer": " Brooks",
        "answer_a": " Brocks",
        "answer_b": " Books",
        "answer_c": " Brooks",
        "answer_d": " Brakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the sitcom Zoey 101, Zoeys brothers name is Todd.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did Lola pretend to be a freaky goth chick on the show Zoey 101?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Has Chase had a crush on Zoey on the sitcom Zoey 101?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did the TV series Zoey 101 hit the airwaves?",
        "correct_answer": " 2005",
        "answer_a": " 2006",
        "answer_b": " 2004",
        "answer_c": " 2005",
        "answer_d": " 2003"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the principal of the high school on Zoey 101?",
        "correct_answer": " Dean Rivers",
        "answer_a": " Mrs Rivers",
        "answer_b": " Dean Matthews",
        "answer_c": " Ms. Matthews",
        "answer_d": " Dean Rivers"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Zoeys high school on Zoey 101?",
        "correct_answer": " PCA",
        "answer_a": " ACP",
        "answer_b": " PAC",
        "answer_c": " PCA",
        "answer_d": " CAP"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Zoeys brainiac friend on the sitcom Zoey 101?",
        "correct_answer": " Quinn",
        "answer_a": " Quinn",
        "answer_b": " Nicole",
        "answer_c": " Ginger",
        "answer_d": " Gretchen"
    },
    {
        "question": "What happened to Nicole on the TV show Zoey 101?",
        "correct_answer": " She went to an all girls school.",
        "answer_a": " She went to an all girls school.",
        "answer_b": " She got expelled.",
        "answer_c": " She moved away.",
        "answer_d": " She went to home school."
    },
    {
        "question": "Logan Ryan is the spoiled rich boy on Zoey 101.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "What  Zoey 101 character has a lisp?",
        "correct_answer": " Stacey",
        "answer_a": " Sally",
        "answer_b": " Sam",
        "answer_c": " Stacey",
        "answer_d": " Sidney"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did Zoey start dating James when Chase went to England.",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Has Quinn dated Marc on the show Zoey 101?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did Zoey 101 end its original run?",
        "correct_answer": " 2008",
        "answer_a": " 2009",
        "answer_b": " 2007",
        "answer_c": " 2006",
        "answer_d": " 2008"
    },
    {
        "question": "Jamie Lynn Spears plays Zoey on Zoey 101.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is there a host for the Arcade on Webkinz?",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " No",
        "answer_b": " Yes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of animal is the school superintendent on Webkinz?",
        "correct_answer": " cow",
        "answer_a": " cow",
        "answer_b": " panda",
        "answer_c": " bear",
        "answer_d": " monkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "On Webkinz, there is a host for the Tournament Area.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many tokens do you need to access the Wish Machine in Webkinz World?",
        "correct_answer": " 10",
        "answer_a": " 2",
        "answer_b": " 5",
        "answer_c": " 15",
        "answer_d": " 10"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dr. Quacks Clinic is the doctors office in Webkinz world.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Webkinz World, What is the maximum amount of Kinzcash (from the tips can) that Arte will accept?",
        "correct_answer": " 100",
        "answer_a": " 100",
        "answer_b": " 10",
        "answer_c": " 1",
        "answer_d": " 50"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 150th to last word in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        "correct_answer": " Both",
        "answer_a": " Ginny",
        "answer_b": " Both",
        "answer_c": " Harry",
        "answer_d": " Said"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, there is a chapter called The Bribe. What is the 138th word in this chapter?",
        "correct_answer": " They",
        "answer_a": " They",
        "answer_b": " Aberforth",
        "answer_c": " Came",
        "answer_d": " Hallows"
    },
    {
        "question": "This word is the 367th word of Hermiones Secret in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.",
        "correct_answer": " By",
        "answer_a": " It",
        "answer_b": " The",
        "answer_c": " By",
        "answer_d": " Hermione"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 120th word in Grim Defeat, a chapter of Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.",
        "correct_answer": " Send",
        "answer_a": " Sirius",
        "answer_b": " Grim",
        "answer_c": " Send",
        "answer_d": " Letter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the 105th to last word in Diagon Alley, a chapter in Harry Potter and the Sorcerers/Philosophers Stone?",
        "correct_answer": " Great",
        "answer_a": " Happy",
        "answer_b": " Hedwig",
        "answer_c": " Great",
        "answer_d": " Hagrid"
    },
    {
        "question": "This word is the 224th word of the chapter, titled The Midnight Duel in Harry Potter and the Sorcerers/Philosophers Stone.",
        "correct_answer": " Everyone",
        "answer_a": " Snake",
        "answer_b": " Filch",
        "answer_c": " Malfoy",
        "answer_d": " Everyone"
    },
    {
        "question": "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets has a chapter called The Chamber of Secrets. What is the 83rd to last word in this chapter?",
        "correct_answer": " Serpents",
        "answer_a": " Riddle",
        "answer_b": " Rocks",
        "answer_c": " Lockhart",
        "answer_d": " Serpents"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Dueling Club, a chapter in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, what is the 251st to last word?",
        "correct_answer": " Tongue",
        "answer_a": " Wand",
        "answer_b": " Malfoy",
        "answer_c": " Ron",
        "answer_d": " Tongue"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is word number 230 in the chapter Elf Tails in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
        "correct_answer": " Throat",
        "answer_a": " Anyone",
        "answer_b": " Throat",
        "answer_c": " Elf",
        "answer_d": " Harry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whats the last line of the nursery rhyme Little Bo Peep:",
        "answer_a": "nd cant tell where to find them.",
        "correct_answer": " Wagging their tails behind them",
        "answer_b": " Sooner then you think",
        "answer_c": " Waiting for their mommy",
        "answer_d": " Wagging their tails behind them"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fill in the missing words in the nursery rhyme Hush, Little Baby:",
        "correct_answer": " A diamond ring",
        "answer_a": " A diamond ring",
        "answer_b": " A cart and bull",
        "answer_c": " A billy goat",
        "answer_d": " A looking glass"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the following division problem, the quotient is 2:",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "If your dog is licking him/herself, he/she is actually doing this.",
        "correct_answer": " Taking a bath",
        "answer_a": " Scratching him/herself",
        "answer_b": " Trying to get attention",
        "answer_c": " Playing around",
        "answer_d": " Taking a bath"
    },
    {
        "question": "Kittens use the litter box as a place to what?",
        "correct_answer": " Use the bathroom in",
        "answer_a": " Play in",
        "answer_b": " Sleep in",
        "answer_c": " Use the bathroom in",
        "answer_d": " Eat in"
    },
    {
        "question": "When dogs lick you, to them it is the same as kissing you.",
        "correct_answer": " No",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is NOT true about an adverb?",
        "correct_answer": " modifies nouns",
        "answer_a": " modifies clauses",
        "answer_b": " modifies nouns",
        "answer_c": " modifies adjectives",
        "answer_d": " modifies verbs"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the participle in the following sentence?  Jane noticed her father walking along the shoreline.",
        "correct_answer": " walking",
        "answer_a": " her",
        "answer_b": " along",
        "answer_c": " walking",
        "answer_d": " Jane"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following words can be used as an adjective?",
        "correct_answer": " lazy",
        "answer_a": " door",
        "answer_b": " mom",
        "answer_c": " lazy",
        "answer_d": " car"
    },
    {
        "question": "Two words can be brought together as a compound word.  They can be written together (one way), written as one word (hairstylist) or written with a hyphen (forty-two).  Which of the following sentences is a correct usage of a hyphen?",
        "correct_answer": " Josh was driving down a one-way street.",
        "answer_a": " Josh could only go one-way.",
        "answer_b": " The cherries were chocolate-covered.",
        "answer_c": " Edgar Allen Poe is well-known.",
        "answer_d": " Josh was driving down a one-way street."
    },
    {
        "question": "The word effect is used as what part of speech in the following sentence?  Will lack of sleep have an effect on your performance at work?",
        "correct_answer": " noun",
        "answer_a": " noun",
        "answer_b": " adjective",
        "answer_c": " adverb",
        "answer_d": " verb"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following sentences uses a comma incorrectly?",
        "correct_answer": " Preparing and submitting his report to the review board for evaluation and possible publication, was one of the most difficult tasks Bill had ever attempted.",
        "answer_a": " To stay in shape for competition, athletes must exercise on a regular basis to ensure top performance.",
        "answer_b": " Most of the evidence seemed convincing. Still, the credibility of some witnesses was in question.",
        "answer_c": " Preparing and submitting his report to the review board for evaluation and possible publication, was one of the most difficult tasks Bill had ever attempted.",
        "answer_d": " After the adjustment for inflation, real wages have decreased while corporate profits have grown."
    },
    {
        "question": "In which movie did Hermione Granger say the following:",
        "correct_answer": " Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone",
        "answer_a": " Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
        "answer_b": " Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
        "answer_c": " Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone",
        "answer_d": " Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"
    },
    {
        "question": "Complete this line from the classic childrens book Green Eggs and Ham:",
        "correct_answer": " Sam",
        "answer_a": " Bam-Bam",
        "answer_b": " Jean-Claude Van Damme",
        "answer_c": " Sam",
        "answer_d": " A Lamb"
    },
    {
        "question": "Complete this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham:",
        "correct_answer": " Fox",
        "answer_a": " Clock",
        "answer_b": " Dog with Chicken Pox",
        "answer_c": " Bag of Rocks",
        "answer_d": " Fox"
    },
    {
        "question": "What word is missing in this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham:",
        "correct_answer": " Car",
        "answer_a": " Jeep",
        "answer_b": " Car",
        "answer_c": " Line at the DMV",
        "answer_d": " Bucket of boiled beets"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what Disney film does the following exchange take place:",
        "correct_answer": " Beauty and the Beast",
        "answer_a": " The Black Cauldron",
        "answer_b": " Sleeping Beauty",
        "answer_c": " Lady and the Tramp",
        "answer_d": " Beauty and the Beast"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Disney film is this dialogue from:",
        "answer_d": " A Goofy Movie",
        "answer_b": " The Brave Little Toaster",
        "correct_answer": " The Emperors New Groove",
        "answer_a": " The Emperors New Groove",
        "answer_c": " Mulan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does x equal in this equation?",
        "correct_answer": " 2",
        "answer_a": " 4",
        "answer_b": " 2",
        "answer_c": " 8",
        "answer_d": " 6"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the answer to the following:",
        "correct_answer": " 5",
        "answer_a": " 0",
        "answer_b": " 5",
        "answer_c": " 10",
        "answer_d": " 2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is this correct?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the missing number?",
        "correct_answer": " 16",
        "answer_a": " 16",
        "answer_b": " 17",
        "answer_c": " 14",
        "answer_d": " 15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did the animated series The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius 1st air?",
        "correct_answer": " 2002",
        "answer_a": " 2001",
        "answer_b": " 2000",
        "answer_c": " 2002",
        "answer_d": " 2003"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who  are Jimmys best friends on the show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
        "correct_answer": " Carl and Sheen",
        "answer_a": " Carl and Bolbi",
        "answer_b": " Carl and Sheen",
        "answer_c": " Bolbi and Nick",
        "answer_d": " Sheen and Bob"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are Libbys and Cindys last names on the animated show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
        "correct_answer": " Folfax and Vortex",
        "answer_a": " Johnson and Vortex",
        "answer_b": " Folfax and Vortex",
        "answer_c": " Weed and Anderson",
        "answer_d": " Williams and Washington"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what episode of The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius are Jimmy and friends diagnosed with superpowers?",
        "correct_answer": " The N-Men",
        "answer_a": " Super  Justice League",
        "answer_b": " The Tomorrow Boys",
        "answer_c": " The N-Men",
        "answer_d": " Fundemonium"
    },
    {
        "question": "On the animated show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius, who is Sheens favorite  superhero?",
        "correct_answer": " UltraLord",
        "answer_a": " Bat Man",
        "answer_b": " UltraLord",
        "answer_c": " Speed Boy",
        "answer_d": " Super Man"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city do Jimmy and his friends live in on the show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
        "correct_answer": " Retroville",
        "answer_a": " Oak Town",
        "answer_b": " Retro Park",
        "answer_c": " Retroland",
        "answer_d": " Retroville"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the series The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius, Jimmy has a crush on Cindy.",
        "correct_answer": " True",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Jimmys dads name on The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
        "correct_answer": " Hugh",
        "answer_a": " Robert",
        "answer_b": " James",
        "answer_c": " Joseph",
        "answer_d": " Hugh"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Jimmys dads favorite food on The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
        "correct_answer": " pie",
        "answer_a": " pie",
        "answer_b": " cookies",
        "answer_c": " pizza",
        "answer_d": " cake"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the teacher of fictional character Jimmy Neutron?",
        "correct_answer": " Ms. Fowl",
        "answer_a": " Ms. Fowl",
        "answer_b": " Mrs. Poultry",
        "answer_c": " Ms. Turkey",
        "answer_d": " Ms. Chicken"
    },
    {
        "question": "Does animated character Jimmy Neutron have a  brother?",
        "correct_answer": " Yes",
        "answer_a": " Yes",
        "answer_b": " No"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is a rational fear according to the book the The Wide Window by Lemony Snicket?",
        "correct_answer": " Fear of monsters under your bed",
        "answer_a": " Fear of monsters under your bed",
        "answer_b": " Fear of lemon meringue pie",
        "answer_c": " Fear of heights",
        "answer_d": " Fear of realtors"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the book The Austere Academy, when Carmelita Spats called the Baudelaires cakesniffers, Mr. Poe said that was very rude of her.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " True",
        "answer_b": " False"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which book by Lemony Snicket does the phrase, It takes a village to raise a child, affect the Baudelaires?",
        "correct_answer": " The Vile Village",
        "answer_a": " The Penultimate Peril",
        "answer_b": " The Wide Window",
        "answer_c": " The Vile Village",
        "answer_d": " The Bad Beginning"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement is true about some of the pages of the book The Ersatz Elevator?",
        "correct_answer": " They are just rectangles of black.",
        "answer_a": " They are just rectangles of black.",
        "answer_b": " They look like someone spilled tea on them.",
        "answer_c": " They can only be read if you hold the book up to a mirror.",
        "answer_d": " They are deliberately placed out of order."
    },
    {
        "question": "In which book of A Series of Unfortunate Events are there two pages that are almost identical?",
        "correct_answer": " The Carnivorous Carnival",
        "answer_a": " The Carnivorous Carnival",
        "answer_b": " The Reptile Room",
        "answer_c": " The Grim Grotto",
        "answer_d": " The Vile Village"
    },
    {
        "question": "Every book of A Series of Unfortunate Events is dedicated to Beatrice, followed by a short message. Which of the following sentences was never written on the dedication page?",
        "correct_answer": " To Beatrice, I always used to sleep late on weekends. Alas, now you do, also.",
        "answer_a": " To Beatrice, when I first saw you, I was breathless. Now, you are.",
        "answer_b": " To Beatrice, summer without you is as cold as winter. Winter without you is even colder.",
        "answer_c": " To Beatrice, I always used to sleep late on weekends. Alas, now you do, also.",
        "answer_d": " To Beatrice, you will always be in my mind, in my heart, and in your grave."
    },
    {
        "question": "Decode the name of this fruit:",
        "correct_answer": " Nectarine",
        "answer_a": " Ratennice",
        "answer_b": " Centarine",
        "answer_c": " Nectarine",
        "answer_d": " Nernatice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Beatrice that writer Lemony Snicket always dedicates his books to?",
        "correct_answer": " Beatrice Baudelaire",
        "answer_a": " A metaphor for V. F. D.",
        "answer_b": " Beatrice Quagmire",
        "answer_c": " Beatrice Baudelaire",
        "answer_d": " Aunt Josephines sister"
    },
    {
        "question": "The 13th book of A Series of Unfortunate Events ends with the Baudelaires doing what?",
        "correct_answer": " Sailing on a boat",
        "answer_a": " Settling on an island",
        "answer_b": " Crying",
        "answer_c": " Sailing on a boat",
        "answer_d": " Dying"
    },
    {
        "question": "The final 13th book of A Series of Unfortunate Events has 13 chapters and ends with an About the author... section.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which set of characters from A Series of Unfortunate Events contains only people who lived through the entire series?",
        "correct_answer": " Klaus Baudelaire, Sunny Baudelaire, Duncan Quagmire",
        "answer_a": " Count Olaf, Mr. Baudelaire, Carmelita Spats",
        "answer_b": " Violet Baudelaire, Jerome Squalor, Aunt Josephine",
        "answer_c": " Violet Baudelaire, Klaus Baudelaire, Beatrice Snicket",
        "answer_d": " Klaus Baudelaire, Sunny Baudelaire, Duncan Quagmire"
    },
    {
        "question": "Esme Squalors evilness was due to her boyfriend, Count Olaf.",
        "correct_answer": " False",
        "answer_a": " False",
        "answer_b": " True"
    },
    {
        "question": "In A Series of Unfortunate Events, what type of game did Fionas brother invent?",
        "correct_answer": " Card game",
        "answer_a": " Ball game",
        "answer_b": " Card game",
        "answer_c": " Board game",
        "answer_d": " Word game"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which three names can J.S. stand for in the books of A Series of Unfortunate Events?",
        "correct_answer": " Jaques Snicket, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss",
        "answer_a": " Jaques Snicket, Joseph Spat, Judy Spree",
        "answer_b": " Jaques Snicket, Judy Spree, Justice Strauss",
        "answer_c": " Jaques Snicket, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss",
        "answer_d": " Joseph Spat, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which book of A Series of Unfortunate Events did Klauss glasses break?",
        "correct_answer": " Book 4",
        "answer_a": " Book 4",
        "answer_b": " Book 5",
        "answer_c": " Book 2",
        "answer_d": " Book 3"
    }
]